<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="22795592" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2014-04-01T19:52:23.020" Score="0" ViewCount="149" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have two websites - I say &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; have, but what I mean is that someone else has one which does not fall in my domain and I have one, which is more like a portal. On the portal, we allow registrations for new users. On the website, they are allowing registrations of new users that I should process. Rather than sending their users to our portal, they'd like to just have the registration form built right into their site. I don't want the responsibility of maintaining the styling of the form so that it fits with their site theme/branding, but I'm happy for them to just transmit an HTTP POST to the portal for me to process and store, and respond with either a 200: OK or a 500: Internal Server Error with any errors tagged on so that they can relay errors to the user and have the user correct them and resubmit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Things I do know about their site (let's call it &lt;a href=&quot;http://their.site.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://their.site.com/&lt;/a&gt;) is that it's all HTML5/jQuery. There's nothing presently going on behind the scenes. In fact, currently, their form action just posts to email. I'd like to have an AJAX request just post the form data to me to process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The portal that I'm in control of is ASP.NET MVC4. It presently uses the standard HtmlHelper.AntiForgeryToken in the view and [ValidateAntiForgeryToken] on the controller action to help prevent XSRF.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, that's my starting point...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get where I need to go, I think I understand parts of the process, but not others. I know that &lt;a href=&quot;http://their.site.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://their.site.com/&lt;/a&gt; will need to add headers to the website configuration on their web server to allow this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Access-Control-Allow-Origin: &lt;a href=&quot;http://my.portal.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://my.portal.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Access-Control-Allow-Methods: POST&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tells the user's web browser, that for this page (well, for any page delivered by this web server), HTTP POST to my.portal.com is allowed. Will that allow them to submit a POST by Javascript/jQuery? The information I've found on that seems very conflicted. Some sources say you can still only do a jQuery GET, others suggest you can do a full POST, while others say you still can't do that at all and can only do a full form POST. So, some clarity on that would be really helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, I don't want to just blindly accept POSTs from all domains, so what is the current best practice for me to secure things at the portal end to allow cross origin requests from this site, without opening myself up to the entire world? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My first thoughts were:&#xA;  - To have some mechanism that allows the page on their site to retrieve the AntiForgeryToken form field and cookie that the page would have had if it had been served by my site. But I'm not sure how to deliver that as I'm not serving the form. &#xA;  - I can use an image GET to have my.portal.com to serve up the cookie, but then how do they POST it with the form data and is HTTP_REFERER enough of a validation that the request for the token is authentic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Further info: I only need to support IE10, Firefox and Chrome, so cross browser compatibility isn't as big an issue as it might otherwise be.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;References to blog posts or other material that enables this behaviour in a secure fashion seem to be eluding me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40650" LastActivityDate="2014-04-01T19:52:23.020" Title="What's the best approach to allow valid cross origin resource sharing?" Tags="&lt;jquery&gt;&lt;asp.net&gt;&lt;asp.net-mvc-4&gt;&lt;cors&gt;&lt;csrf&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="11" />
  <row Id="17329142" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="17329233" CreationDate="2013-06-26T19:48:21.873" Score="3" ViewCount="219" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am doing the following, but it is not working properly:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    my $enabled = $hash &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;                  $hash-&amp;gt;{'key'} &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;                  $hash-&amp;gt;{'key'}-&amp;gt;{'enabled'} &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;                  $hash-&amp;gt;{'key'}-&amp;gt;{'active'};&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is this an acceptable way to assign a boolean value to a scalar variable?&#xA;My code is misbehaving in strange ways, as it is, and I believe it is because of this assignment. I have validated that the individual values exist for all of these keys and are set to a value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;P.S. Sorry for being a noob! I googled for ~10 minutes and couldn't find the answer anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1440820" LastActivityDate="2013-06-26T20:02:35.943" Title="How can I assign a boolean condition result to a scalar variable in perl?" Tags="&lt;perl&gt;&lt;hash&gt;&lt;boolean&gt;&lt;condition&gt;&lt;scalar&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="27296440" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="27244323" CreationDate="2014-12-04T14:24:56.303" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Consumer End point always expecting some Input data.&lt;br&gt;For Example You have declared JMS Consumer Endpoint whenever the JMS Queues receive the message then route get activated and its calls next processor which is defined next to consumer end point.&lt;br&gt;But In your case , you have declared direct consumer endpoint so some producer endpoint should send message to Direct endpoint.&lt;br&gt; So Here we are using ProducerTemplate in java DSL to send message to Direct endpoint.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Spring DSL example :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;route id=&quot;parent&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;from uri=&quot;file:location&quot;/&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;to uri=&quot;direct:start&quot;/&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;route/ &amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;route id=&quot;child&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;from uri=&quot;direct:start&quot;/&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;to uri=&quot;bean:textProcessor&quot;/&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;route/ &amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here we have  parent and child route once parent route get the file form defined location it send it to the direct endpoint in the parent route.&lt;br&gt;child route consumer end point is direct so now message will come to child route.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4272769" LastActivityDate="2014-12-04T14:24:56.303" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="17492469" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="17492380" CreationDate="2013-07-05T15:35:21.740" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Try this one:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;'...&#xA;SELECT &#xA;CHAR(34) + [MobilePhoneNumber] + CHAR(34)&#xA;...'&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;'...&#xA;SELECT &#xA;''&quot;'' + [MobilePhoneNumber] + ''&quot;''&#xA;...'&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1689180" LastActivityDate="2013-07-05T15:35:21.740" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1129180" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="1130598" CreationDate="2009-07-15T03:00:19.547" Score="20" ViewCount="3137" Body="&lt;p&gt;When packaging a Python package with a setup.py that uses the setuptools:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;from setuptools import setup&#xA;...&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the source distribution created by:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;python setup.py sdist&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;not only includes, as usual, the files specified in MANIFEST.in, but it also, gratuitously, includes all of the files that Subversion lists as being version controlled beneath the package directory. This is vastly annoying. Not only does it make it difficult to exercise any sort of explicit control over what files get distributed with my package, but it means that when I build my package following an &quot;svn export&quot; instead of an &quot;svn checkout&quot;, the contents of my package might be quite different, since without the .svn metadata setuptools will make different choices about what to include.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My question: how can I turn off this terrible behavior, so that &quot;setuptools&quot; treats my project the same way whether I'm using Subversion, or version control it's never heard of, or a bare tree created with &quot;svn export&quot; that I've created at the end of my project to make sure it builds cleanly somewhere besides my working directory?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The best I have managed so far is an ugly monkey-patch:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;from setuptools.command import sdist&#xA;del sdist.finders[:]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But this is Python, not the jungle, so of course I want a better solution that involves no monkeys at all. How can I tame setuptools, turn off its magic, and have it behave sensibly by looking at the visible, predictable rules in my MANIFEST.py instead?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="85360" LastActivityDate="2009-12-24T22:24:50.377" Title="How can I make setuptools ignore subversion inventory?" Tags="&lt;python&gt;&lt;packaging&gt;&lt;setuptools&gt;&lt;egg&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="4" />
  <row Id="37248326" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="33855732" CreationDate="2016-05-16T06:56:46.513" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;you can change user redirect for multi users in following function.&#xA; But incase of laravel version update your change in here may be canceled. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;go to the file path and change function&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;vendor\laravel\framework\src\illuminate\Foundation\Auth\AuthenticatesUser.php &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;protected function handleUserWasAuthenticated(Request $request, $throttles)&#xA;    {&#xA;        if ($throttles) {&#xA;            $this-&amp;gt;clearLoginAttempts($request);&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        if (method_exists($this, 'authenticated')) {&#xA;            return $this-&amp;gt;authenticated($request, Auth::user());&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        $user = Auth::user();&#xA;        $type = $user-&amp;gt;Rtype;&#xA;&#xA;        if($type==1){&#xA;            return redirect()-&amp;gt;intended('/admin/dashboard');&#xA;        }elseif($type==2){&#xA;            return redirect()-&amp;gt;intended('/admin/dashboard');&#xA;        }elseif($type==3){&#xA;            return redirect()-&amp;gt;intended('/');&#xA;        }else{&#xA;        return redirect()-&amp;gt;intended($this-&amp;gt;redirectPath());&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6339509" LastEditorUserId="5771917" LastEditDate="2016-05-16T07:55:34.673" LastActivityDate="2016-05-16T07:55:34.673" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="774062" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="773340" CreationDate="2009-04-21T18:53:56.800" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;language: Python&lt;br&gt;&#xA;library: &lt;a href=&quot;http://codespeak.net/lxml/lxmlhtml.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;lxml.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;import lxml.html&#xA;&#xA;html = &quot;&amp;lt;html&amp;gt;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&quot;&#xA;for link in (&quot;foo&quot;, &quot;bar&quot;, &quot;baz&quot;):&#xA;    html += '&amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://%s.com&quot;&amp;gt;%s&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;' % (link, link)&#xA;html += &quot;&amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/html&amp;gt;&quot;&#xA;&#xA;tree = lxml.html.document_fromstring(html)&#xA;for element, attribute, link, pos in tree.iterlinks():&#xA;    if attribute == &quot;href&quot;:&#xA;        print link&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;lxml also has a CSS selector class for traversing the DOM, which can make using it very similar to using JQuery:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;for a in tree.cssselect('a[href]'):&#xA;    print a.get('href')&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56219" LastEditorUserId="34258" LastEditDate="2009-04-21T22:51:05.733" LastActivityDate="2009-04-21T22:51:05.733" CommentCount="3" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-04-21T18:53:56.800" />
  <row Id="16045359" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="15944620" CreationDate="2013-04-16T19:21:15.437" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I finally had the sense to re-install Google app-engine's latest version which was compatible with 1.77. Whatever the problem was it was solved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Too all Google representatives: some newbies like me are not familiar with the command line. I recommend you add the uninstall option for the app-engine and any files outside the eclipse plugin.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1447071" LastActivityDate="2013-04-16T19:21:15.437" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="18969846" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="18969872" CreationDate="2013-09-23T22:18:04.653" Score="0" ViewCount="42" Body="&lt;p&gt;I need a little logic help as well as some code help. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm writing a program that is suppose to be a simple ATM program.&#xA;It will do deposits&#xA;Withdrawals&#xA;And a balance check.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also have to have my program record the date of every deposit, and use that date when calculating 5% interest over a year for when the user checks their balance. The part im having problems with is the part where I need to store the deposit amount as well as the date that corresponds to that deposit. I'm supposed to use the GregorianCalender methods.  Im just taking a shot in the dark but I think I would use an array for this. But im clueless as to how to implement it. Because I'm new to arrays. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just to give u an idea. I have my Main class. A menu class, and a transaction class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2733862" LastActivityDate="2013-09-23T22:20:29.023" Title="Need to store a double with a date. I'm thinking array but am Unsure" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;arrays&gt;&lt;transactions&gt;&lt;calendar&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="43990117" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43984738" CreationDate="2017-05-15T23:07:52.690" Score="1" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;listMax :: Ord a =&amp;gt; [a] -&amp;gt; a&#xA;listMax [] = error &quot;Tried to find maximum of an empty list.&quot;&#xA;listMax (x:xs) = listMax' xs x where&#xA;  listMax' :: Ord a =&amp;gt; [a] -&amp;gt; a -&amp;gt; a&#xA;  listMax' [] y = y&#xA;  listMax' (x:xs) y | x &amp;gt; y     = listMax' xs x&#xA;                    | otherwise = listMax' xs y&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this case, y is the accumulating parameter that holds the maximum value found so far.  Brief proof of correctness: the algorithm terminates because each tail-recursive call removes one element from the input list until it is empty.  The final value of &lt;code&gt;y&lt;/code&gt; it returns is the maximum because, for every other element &lt;code&gt;x&lt;/code&gt; in the input, either &lt;code&gt;y &amp;gt; x&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;y &amp;gt; z &amp;gt; x&lt;/code&gt; for some &lt;code&gt;z&lt;/code&gt; after &lt;code&gt;x&lt;/code&gt; and before &lt;code&gt;y&lt;/code&gt;.  (This assumes that &lt;code&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is transitive.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You could also write the helper function this way:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;listMax' :: Ord a =&amp;gt; [a] -&amp;gt; a -&amp;gt; a&#xA;listMax' [] y = y&#xA;listMax' (x:xs) y = listMax' xs (max x y)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And this implementation does the same thing:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;listMax2 :: Ord a =&amp;gt; [a] -&amp;gt; a&#xA;listMax2 [] = error &quot;Tried to find maximum of an empty list.&quot;&#xA;listMax2 list = foldl1 max list&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;foldl1&lt;/code&gt; function is a tail-recursive lazy evaluation from front to back, but the strict &lt;code&gt;foldl1'&lt;/code&gt; version or &lt;code&gt;foldr1&lt;/code&gt; might be more efficient in this case.  The first version is closer to strict evaluation than lazy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4474419" LastEditorUserId="4474419" LastEditDate="2017-05-18T00:17:59.123" LastActivityDate="2017-05-18T00:17:59.123" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="15135904" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T12:45:47.533" Score="0" ViewCount="2559" Body="&lt;p&gt;We need to implement export to excel/word/pdf functionality for reporting in SharePoint. What would be the suitable solution for this. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.c-sharpcorner.com/uploadfile/eb5fab/export-data-in-Asp-Net-gridview-to-doc-gridview-to-excel-gridview-to-pdf/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.c-sharpcorner.com/uploadfile/eb5fab/export-data-in-Asp-Net-gridview-to-doc-gridview-to-excel-gridview-to-pdf/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I go through with the above link. It takes the Grid view and render the output in the  but it is not suitable if we had 10 million records. For the performance point of view it is not good. Can you please help &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="312891" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T12:45:47.533" Title="How to export data to excel/word/pdf in sharepoint 2010?" Tags="&lt;sharepoint-2010&gt;&lt;reporting&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="35431884" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="35432286" CreationDate="2016-02-16T11:52:18.017" Score="0" ViewCount="64" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have table Test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sso     ID&#xA;-------------&#xA;1234    XV&#xA;1235    PL17&#xA;1234    PL17&#xA;1239    XV&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to concatenate all IDs having same sso. I have developed the output using &lt;code&gt;GROUP_CONCAT&lt;/code&gt; function.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is the query&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;SELECT sso, GROUP_CONCAT(ID) FROM samesso GROUP BY sso&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I want to do this without function. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can I have any syggestions or ideas to do this ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5819068" LastEditorUserId="3636601" LastEditDate="2016-02-16T11:58:27.183" LastActivityDate="2016-02-16T12:11:40.397" Title="concat multiple rows in one field" Tags="&lt;mysql&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="19888576" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-11-10T10:22:29.707" Score="19" ViewCount="10949" Body="&lt;p&gt;In a VS 2013 RTM, MVC 5 project with EF 6, I tried to scaffold a controller based on the ApplicationUser (default with individual accounts authentication). Both &lt;code&gt;ApplicationUser&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;IdentityUser&lt;/code&gt; are mapped to a Users table.&#xA;The wizard opens the context file for editing and tries to add a new db set for ApplicationUser (ApplicationUsers) and then fails with this error:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Unable to retrieve metadata for ApplicationUser. Multiple object sets per type are not supported. The object sets ApplicationUsers and Users can both contain instances of type ApplicationUser&lt;/code&gt;&#xA;The solution does not have any reference to, or instance of &lt;code&gt;ApplicationUsers&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is this a known issue? Can the scaffolding be run using command line with options (from PMC)?&#xA;Note: scaffolding also adds an extra db set to the context class if I specify a model that references ApplicationUser (the app works if I remove it and fix references in the generate controller).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2959207" LastEditorUserId="769831" LastEditDate="2014-05-26T09:41:40.850" LastActivityDate="2015-10-01T22:45:37.480" Title="VS 2013 Controller Scaffolding Fails for the ApplicationUser Model (Multiple object sets per type are not supported)" Tags="&lt;scaffolding&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="9" />
  <row Id="22951422" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2014-04-09T01:54:37.780" Score="0" ViewCount="388" Body="&lt;p&gt;Im using JavaEE 7, Glassfish 4, Maven 3.2.1.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have read several posts where users get exact error, which represents wide area of actual problems, as stated here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/18107858/cdi-inject-fails-on-maven-embedded-glassfish-plugin-org-jboss-weld-exceptions&quot;&gt;CDI Inject fails on maven-embedded-glassfish-plugin -- org.jboss.weld.exceptions.DeploymentException: WELD-001408 Unsatisfied dependencies for type&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, how can I determine whats the actual problem? All annotations seem to be correct, as same code works for my teammates on their own machines...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example for project manager, I have interface like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@Local&#xA;public interface ProjectManager { some mtehods...}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;then I have implementation of it like: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@Stateless(mappedName = &quot;projectManager&quot;)&#xA;public class ProjectManagerEJB implements ProjectManager {&#xA;&#xA;    @PersistenceContext(unitName = &quot;scrumkin_PU&quot;)&#xA;    private EntityManager em;&#xA;&#xA;    @Inject&#xA;    private GroupManager gm;&#xA;&#xA;    @Override&#xA;    public void someMethod(...);&#xA;&#xA;    some other methods...&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the RESTful:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@Path(&quot;project&quot;)&#xA;@Stateless&#xA;@Consumes(&quot;application/json&quot;)&#xA;@Produces(&quot;application/json&quot;)&#xA;public class ProjectService {&#xA;&#xA;    @Inject&#xA;    private UserManager um;&#xA;    @Inject&#xA;    private ProjectManager pm;&#xA;&#xA;    @POST&#xA;    public void createProject(ProjectJSON project, @Context HttpServletResponse response) {...} &#xA;&#xA;    some other methods...&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The problem was, I imported project on which I was working on with eclipse, so now I pulled repository into another location and I was able to deploy with IntelliJIDEA (is it possible to use same location of project for Eclipse and IntelliJIDEA (as in, import project in IntelliJIDEA without Eclipse settings (settings files), because they are causing problems)?).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But now, calls to RESTful service are not working, this is what glassfish log looks like after deploying (the warnings part):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[2014-04-11T23:48:57.922+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [] [org.jboss.weld.interceptor.util.InterceptionTypeRegistry] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252937922] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Class 'javax.ejb.PostActivate' not found, interception based on it is not enabled]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:57.923+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [] [org.jboss.weld.interceptor.util.InterceptionTypeRegistry] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252937923] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Class 'javax.ejb.PrePassivate' not found, interception based on it is not enabled]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.643+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [INFO] [] [org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.init.JerseyServletContainerInitializer] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938643] [levelValue: 800] [[&#xA;  Registering the Jersey servlet application, named com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication, at the servlet mapping /*, with the Application class of the same name.]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.698+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [INFO] [AS-WEB-GLUE-00172] [javax.enterprise.web] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938698] [levelValue: 800] [[&#xA;  Loading application [scrumkin-ear-1.0-SNAPSHOT#scrumkin-rs-1.0-SNAPSHOT.war] at [/api]]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.729+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938729] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.730+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938730] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.731+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938731] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.731+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938731] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.732+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938732] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.733+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938733] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.734+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938734] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.734+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938734] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.735+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938735] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.736+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938736] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.736+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938736] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.737+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938737] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.738+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938738] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.739+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938739] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.LoginService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.LoginService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.739+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938739] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.SprintService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.740+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938740] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserStoryService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.741+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938741] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.741+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938741] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.UserService, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.UserService]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.742+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [AS-WEB-UTIL-00035] [javax.enterprise.web.util] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938742] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Unable to load class com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication, reason: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:58.777+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [INFO] [AS-WEB-GLUE-00172] [javax.enterprise.web] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252938777] [levelValue: 800] [[&#xA;  Loading application [scrumkin-ear-1.0-SNAPSHOT#scrumkin-web-1.0-SNAPSHOT.war] at [/]]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:59.125+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [INFO] [] [javax.enterprise.system.core] [tid: _ThreadID=40 _ThreadName=admin-listener(4)] [timeMillis: 1397252939125] [levelValue: 800] [[&#xA;  scrumkin-ear-1.0-SNAPSHOT was successfully deployed in 9.668 milliseconds.]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-11T23:48:59.779+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [] [javax.enterprise.system.container.web.com.sun.web.security] [tid: _ThreadID=23 _ThreadName=http-listener-1(1)] [timeMillis: 1397252939779] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  Context path from ServletContext:  differs from path from bundle: /]]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And when I try to call some valid RESTful path (a GET method), I get:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[2014-04-12T00:05:17.679+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [INFO] [] [org.glassfish.jersey.server.ApplicationHandler] [tid: _ThreadID=27 _ThreadName=http-listener-1(5)] [timeMillis: 1397253917679] [levelValue: 800] [[&#xA;  Initiating Jersey application, version Jersey: 2.0 2013-05-03 14:50:15...]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-12T00:05:17.853+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [INFO] [] [org.glassfish.jersey.gf.ejb.EjbComponentProvider] [tid: _ThreadID=27 _ThreadName=http-listener-1(5)] [timeMillis: 1397253917853] [levelValue: 800] [[&#xA;  The Jersey EJB interceptor is bound. JAX-RS EJB integration support is enabled.]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-12T00:05:18.934+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [ejb.system_exception] [javax.enterprise.system.container.ejb.com.sun.ejb.containers] [tid: _ThreadID=27 _ThreadName=http-listener-1(5)] [timeMillis: 1397253918934] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  EJB5184:A system exception occurred during an invocation on EJB ProjectService, method: public com.scrumkin.rs.json.ProjectJSON com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService.getProject(int)]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-12T00:05:18.934+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [] [javax.enterprise.system.container.ejb.com.sun.ejb.containers] [tid: _ThreadID=27 _ThreadName=http-listener-1(5)] [timeMillis: 1397253918934] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;&#xA;javax.ejb.EJBException&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBContainerTransactionManager.processSystemException(EJBContainerTransactionManager.java:748)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBContainerTransactionManager.completeNewTx(EJBContainerTransactionManager.java:698)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBContainerTransactionManager.postInvokeTx(EJBContainerTransactionManager.java:503)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.postInvokeTx(BaseContainer.java:4475)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.postInvoke(BaseContainer.java:2009)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.postInvoke(BaseContainer.java:1979)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandler.invoke(EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandler.java:220)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandlerDelegate.invoke(EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandlerDelegate.java:88)&#xA;    at com.sun.proxy.$Proxy219.getProject(Unknown Source)&#xA;    at com.scrumkin.rs.__EJB31_Generated__ProjectService__Intf____Bean__.getProject(Unknown Source)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.ResourceMethodInvocationHandlerFactory$1.invoke(ResourceMethodInvocationHandlerFactory.java:81)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.invoke(AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.java:125)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.JavaResourceMethodDispatcherProvider$TypeOutInvoker.doDispatch(JavaResourceMethodDispatcherProvider.java:195)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.dispatch(AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.java:91)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.ResourceMethodInvoker.invoke(ResourceMethodInvoker.java:346)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.ResourceMethodInvoker.apply(ResourceMethodInvoker.java:341)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.ResourceMethodInvoker.apply(ResourceMethodInvoker.java:101)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.ServerRuntime$1.run(ServerRuntime.java:224)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors$1.call(Errors.java:271)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors$1.call(Errors.java:267)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors.process(Errors.java:315)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors.process(Errors.java:297)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors.process(Errors.java:267)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.process.internal.RequestScope.runInScope(RequestScope.java:317)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.ServerRuntime.process(ServerRuntime.java:198)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.ApplicationHandler.handle(ApplicationHandler.java:946)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.WebComponent.service(WebComponent.java:323)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.ServletContainer.service(ServletContainer.java:372)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.ServletContainer.service(ServletContainer.java:335)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.ServletContainer.service(ServletContainer.java:218)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardWrapper.service(StandardWrapper.java:1682)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardWrapperValve.invoke(StandardWrapperValve.java:318)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardContextValve.invoke(StandardContextValve.java:160)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardPipeline.doInvoke(StandardPipeline.java:734)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardPipeline.invoke(StandardPipeline.java:673)&#xA;    at com.sun.enterprise.web.WebPipeline.invoke(WebPipeline.java:99)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardHostValve.invoke(StandardHostValve.java:174)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.connector.CoyoteAdapter.doService(CoyoteAdapter.java:357)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.connector.CoyoteAdapter.service(CoyoteAdapter.java:260)&#xA;    at com.sun.enterprise.v3.services.impl.ContainerMapper.service(ContainerMapper.java:188)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.http.server.HttpHandler.runService(HttpHandler.java:191)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.http.server.HttpHandler.doHandle(HttpHandler.java:168)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.http.server.HttpServerFilter.handleRead(HttpServerFilter.java:189)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.ExecutorResolver$9.execute(ExecutorResolver.java:119)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.executeFilter(DefaultFilterChain.java:288)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.executeChainPart(DefaultFilterChain.java:206)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.execute(DefaultFilterChain.java:136)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.process(DefaultFilterChain.java:114)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.ProcessorExecutor.execute(ProcessorExecutor.java:77)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.nio.transport.TCPNIOTransport.fireIOEvent(TCPNIOTransport.java:838)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.AbstractIOStrategy.fireIOEvent(AbstractIOStrategy.java:113)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.WorkerThreadIOStrategy.run0(WorkerThreadIOStrategy.java:115)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.WorkerThreadIOStrategy.access$100(WorkerThreadIOStrategy.java:55)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.WorkerThreadIOStrategy$WorkerThreadRunnable.run(WorkerThreadIOStrategy.java:135)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.threadpool.AbstractThreadPool$Worker.doWork(AbstractThreadPool.java:564)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.threadpool.AbstractThreadPool$Worker.run(AbstractThreadPool.java:544)&#xA;    at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:744)&#xA;Caused by: java.lang.NullPointerException&#xA;    at com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService.getProject(ProjectService.java:109)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.ejb.security.application.EJBSecurityManager.runMethod(EJBSecurityManager.java:1081)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.ejb.security.application.EJBSecurityManager.invoke(EJBSecurityManager.java:1153)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.invokeBeanMethod(BaseContainer.java:4695)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.EjbInvocation.invokeBeanMethod(EjbInvocation.java:630)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeChainImpl.invokeNext(InterceptorManager.java:822)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.EjbInvocation.proceed(EjbInvocation.java:582)&#xA;    at org.jboss.weld.ejb.AbstractEJBRequestScopeActivationInterceptor.aroundInvoke(AbstractEJBRequestScopeActivationInterceptor.java:46)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeInterceptor.intercept(InterceptorManager.java:883)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeChainImpl.invokeNext(InterceptorManager.java:822)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.EjbInvocation.proceed(EjbInvocation.java:582)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.SystemInterceptorProxy.doCall(SystemInterceptorProxy.java:163)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.SystemInterceptorProxy.aroundInvoke(SystemInterceptorProxy.java:140)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeInterceptor.intercept(InterceptorManager.java:883)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeChainImpl.invokeNext(InterceptorManager.java:822)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.InterceptorManager.intercept(InterceptorManager.java:369)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.__intercept(BaseContainer.java:4667)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.intercept(BaseContainer.java:4655)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandler.invoke(EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandler.java:212)&#xA;    ... 54 more&#xA;]]&#xA;&#xA;[2014-04-12T00:05:18.977+0200] [glassfish 4.0] [WARNING] [] [javax.enterprise.web] [tid: _ThreadID=27 _ThreadName=http-listener-1(5)] [timeMillis: 1397253918977] [levelValue: 900] [[&#xA;  StandardWrapperValve[com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication]: Servlet.service() for servlet com.scrumkin.rs.RESTApplication threw exception&#xA;java.lang.NullPointerException&#xA;    at com.scrumkin.rs.ProjectService.getProject(ProjectService.java:109)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.ejb.security.application.EJBSecurityManager.runMethod(EJBSecurityManager.java:1081)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.ejb.security.application.EJBSecurityManager.invoke(EJBSecurityManager.java:1153)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.invokeBeanMethod(BaseContainer.java:4695)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.EjbInvocation.invokeBeanMethod(EjbInvocation.java:630)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeChainImpl.invokeNext(InterceptorManager.java:822)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.EjbInvocation.proceed(EjbInvocation.java:582)&#xA;    at org.jboss.weld.ejb.AbstractEJBRequestScopeActivationInterceptor.aroundInvoke(AbstractEJBRequestScopeActivationInterceptor.java:46)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeInterceptor.intercept(InterceptorManager.java:883)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeChainImpl.invokeNext(InterceptorManager.java:822)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.EjbInvocation.proceed(EjbInvocation.java:582)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.SystemInterceptorProxy.doCall(SystemInterceptorProxy.java:163)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.SystemInterceptorProxy.aroundInvoke(SystemInterceptorProxy.java:140)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeInterceptor.intercept(InterceptorManager.java:883)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.AroundInvokeChainImpl.invokeNext(InterceptorManager.java:822)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.interceptors.InterceptorManager.intercept(InterceptorManager.java:369)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.__intercept(BaseContainer.java:4667)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.BaseContainer.intercept(BaseContainer.java:4655)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandler.invoke(EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandler.java:212)&#xA;    at com.sun.ejb.containers.EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandlerDelegate.invoke(EJBLocalObjectInvocationHandlerDelegate.java:88)&#xA;    at com.sun.proxy.$Proxy219.getProject(Unknown Source)&#xA;    at com.scrumkin.rs.__EJB31_Generated__ProjectService__Intf____Bean__.getProject(Unknown Source)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke0(Native Method)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.NativeMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(NativeMethodAccessorImpl.java:57)&#xA;    at sun.reflect.DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.invoke(DelegatingMethodAccessorImpl.java:43)&#xA;    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:606)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.ResourceMethodInvocationHandlerFactory$1.invoke(ResourceMethodInvocationHandlerFactory.java:81)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.invoke(AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.java:125)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.JavaResourceMethodDispatcherProvider$TypeOutInvoker.doDispatch(JavaResourceMethodDispatcherProvider.java:195)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.internal.AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.dispatch(AbstractJavaResourceMethodDispatcher.java:91)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.ResourceMethodInvoker.invoke(ResourceMethodInvoker.java:346)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.ResourceMethodInvoker.apply(ResourceMethodInvoker.java:341)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.model.ResourceMethodInvoker.apply(ResourceMethodInvoker.java:101)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.ServerRuntime$1.run(ServerRuntime.java:224)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors$1.call(Errors.java:271)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors$1.call(Errors.java:267)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors.process(Errors.java:315)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors.process(Errors.java:297)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.internal.Errors.process(Errors.java:267)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.process.internal.RequestScope.runInScope(RequestScope.java:317)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.ServerRuntime.process(ServerRuntime.java:198)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.server.ApplicationHandler.handle(ApplicationHandler.java:946)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.WebComponent.service(WebComponent.java:323)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.ServletContainer.service(ServletContainer.java:372)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.ServletContainer.service(ServletContainer.java:335)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.jersey.servlet.ServletContainer.service(ServletContainer.java:218)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardWrapper.service(StandardWrapper.java:1682)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardWrapperValve.invoke(StandardWrapperValve.java:318)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardContextValve.invoke(StandardContextValve.java:160)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardPipeline.doInvoke(StandardPipeline.java:734)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardPipeline.invoke(StandardPipeline.java:673)&#xA;    at com.sun.enterprise.web.WebPipeline.invoke(WebPipeline.java:99)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.core.StandardHostValve.invoke(StandardHostValve.java:174)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.connector.CoyoteAdapter.doService(CoyoteAdapter.java:357)&#xA;    at org.apache.catalina.connector.CoyoteAdapter.service(CoyoteAdapter.java:260)&#xA;    at com.sun.enterprise.v3.services.impl.ContainerMapper.service(ContainerMapper.java:188)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.http.server.HttpHandler.runService(HttpHandler.java:191)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.http.server.HttpHandler.doHandle(HttpHandler.java:168)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.http.server.HttpServerFilter.handleRead(HttpServerFilter.java:189)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.ExecutorResolver$9.execute(ExecutorResolver.java:119)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.executeFilter(DefaultFilterChain.java:288)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.executeChainPart(DefaultFilterChain.java:206)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.execute(DefaultFilterChain.java:136)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.filterchain.DefaultFilterChain.process(DefaultFilterChain.java:114)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.ProcessorExecutor.execute(ProcessorExecutor.java:77)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.nio.transport.TCPNIOTransport.fireIOEvent(TCPNIOTransport.java:838)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.AbstractIOStrategy.fireIOEvent(AbstractIOStrategy.java:113)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.WorkerThreadIOStrategy.run0(WorkerThreadIOStrategy.java:115)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.WorkerThreadIOStrategy.access$100(WorkerThreadIOStrategy.java:55)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.strategies.WorkerThreadIOStrategy$WorkerThreadRunnable.run(WorkerThreadIOStrategy.java:135)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.threadpool.AbstractThreadPool$Worker.doWork(AbstractThreadPool.java:564)&#xA;    at org.glassfish.grizzly.threadpool.AbstractThreadPool$Worker.run(AbstractThreadPool.java:544)&#xA;    at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:744)&#xA;]]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2340939" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T10:26:03.837" LastActivityDate="2014-04-11T22:11:54.470" Title="IntelliJIDEA WELD-001408 exception when trying to deploy javaEE maven packed application on glassfish" Tags="&lt;maven&gt;&lt;java-ee&gt;&lt;intellij-idea&gt;&lt;glassfish&gt;&lt;dependencies&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="8" />
  <row Id="15775570" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="15775535" CreationDate="2013-04-02T22:28:23.650" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;When chaining you'll do:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;if ( container.has('div') ) {...}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="965051" LastEditorUserId="965051" LastEditDate="2013-04-02T22:37:56.903" LastActivityDate="2013-04-02T22:37:56.903" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="41820880" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="41820650" CreationDate="2017-01-24T05:49:38.173" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is out of the MobileFirst Platform control, as it cannot control the status / version of the WebView provided by the Android system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know that recently Google released updated Chrome WebView (versions 53 and 54) which contain several bugs. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you've mentioned, you can uninstall this (or update it, from the Google Play Store), and this is an action that has to be done by the end-user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only known workaround is for the end user to update the WebView from the Play Store (if it is not auto-updated). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To iterate, from the MobileFirst Platform framework perspective, the application consumes the WebView that is provided by the OS and therefore has no control over the behaviour of the WebView. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you can request users to update the WebView by sending a notification from the MobileFirst Console, a push notification and alike.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1530814" LastActivityDate="2017-01-24T05:49:38.173" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="9719551" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9719447" CreationDate="2012-03-15T12:20:03.410" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Looks like you've accidentally connected a view to your application instance rather than your view controller. Since &lt;code&gt;UIApplication&lt;/code&gt; has no &lt;code&gt;view&lt;/code&gt; property, this throws an error when the nib file is loaded. Remove that connection and you should be fine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="23649" LastActivityDate="2012-03-15T12:20:03.410" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="14263099" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14263032" CreationDate="2013-01-10T16:52:42.323" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is not possible because you're trying to make cross-domain request.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;you might want to check out JSONP as a solution instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out this &lt;a href=&quot;http://remysharp.com/2007/10/08/what-is-jsonp/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://remysharp.com/2007/10/08/what-is-jsonp/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1750604" LastActivityDate="2013-01-10T16:52:42.323" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="24380715" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="24380326" CreationDate="2014-06-24T07:25:14.187" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You could use a character class also,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;gt; var res = text.match(/([0-9\.]+)(\w+)/);&#xA;undefined&#xA;&amp;gt; res[1]&#xA;'4.66'&#xA;&amp;gt; res[2]&#xA;'lb'&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3297613" LastActivityDate="2014-06-24T07:25:14.187" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="27230000" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="27190313" CreationDate="2014-12-01T13:59:51.457" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Twitter Kit has the ability to make API calls. The official documentation is here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.twitter.com/twitter-kit/android/api&quot;&gt;https://dev.twitter.com/twitter-kit/android/api&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everything starts with Statuses Service:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;StatusService service = Twitter.getApiClient().getStatusesService()&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some methods available at Statuses Service (these methods have direct mapping to REST API endpoints, including the parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;service.homeTimeline();&#xA;service.lookup();&#xA;service.mentionsTimeline();&#xA;service.show();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The mechanism to do a request is similar to all services, here's an example of Searching from &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/twitterdev/cannonball-android/blob/master/app/src/main/java/io/fabric/samples/cannonball/activity/PoemPopularActivity.java&quot;&gt;Cannonball sample app code&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;final SearchService service = Twitter.getApiClient().getSearchService();&#xA;&#xA;service.tweets(SEARCH_QUERY, null, null, null, SEARCH_RESULT_TYPE, SEARCH_COUNT, null, null,&#xA;            maxId, true, new Callback&amp;lt;Search&amp;gt;() {&#xA;                @Override&#xA;                public void success(Result&amp;lt;Search&amp;gt; searchResult) {&#xA;                    Crashlytics.setLong(App.CRASHLYTICS_KEY_SEARCH_COUNT,&#xA;                            searchResult.data.searchMetadata.count);&#xA;                    setProgressBarIndeterminateVisibility(false);&#xA;                    final List&amp;lt;Tweet&amp;gt; tweets = searchResult.data.tweets;&#xA;                    adapter.getTweets().addAll(tweets);&#xA;                    adapter.notifyDataSetChanged();&#xA;                    if (tweets.size() &amp;gt; 0) {&#xA;                        maxId = tweets.get(tweets.size() - 1).id - 1;&#xA;                    } else {&#xA;                        endOfSearchResults = true;&#xA;                    }&#xA;                    flagLoading = false;&#xA;                }&#xA;&#xA;                @Override&#xA;                public void failure(TwitterException error) {&#xA;                    Crashlytics.logException(error);&#xA;&#xA;                    setProgressBarIndeterminateVisibility(false);&#xA;                    Toast.makeText(PoemPopularActivity.this,&#xA;                            getResources().getString(R.string.toast_retrieve_tweets_error),&#xA;                            Toast.LENGTH_SHORT).show();&#xA;&#xA;                    flagLoading = false;&#xA;                }&#xA;            }&#xA;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50882" LastActivityDate="2014-12-01T13:59:51.457" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="19988839" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-11-14T21:32:32.227" Score="0" ViewCount="680" Body="&lt;p&gt;i am trying with below code but it is failing with error : Uncaught SyntaxError: Unexpected identifier, on the line :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$.get(&quot;commonCore/templates/&quot; + data[i].templateHtml ,function(html)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;can somebody please help me debugging it. i am very much new to javascript and jquery&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JSON :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[{&quot;templateHtml&quot;:&quot;dashBoardLeftInsight.html&quot;,&quot;classSelect&quot;:&quot;leftpanel&quot;},{&quot;templateHtml&quot;:&quot;dcdcsFilterOptions.html&quot;,&quot;classSelect&quot;:&quot;dcdcsOptions&quot;},{&quot;templateHtml&quot;:&quot;advanceFilterOptions.html&quot;,&quot;classSelect&quot;:&quot;advancedOptions&quot;},{&quot;templateHtml&quot;:&quot;reportFilterOptions.html&quot;,&quot;classSelect&quot;:&quot;reportdashboard&quot;}]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;code :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$.getJSON('api/filterTemplate/dashboard',function (data){&#xA;&#xA;            var a = new Array(data.length);&#xA;            console.log(data.length);&#xA;&#xA;                $.when(function(){&#xA;                    for(var i=0;i&amp;lt;=data.length,i++)&#xA;                    {&#xA;                        $.get(&quot;commonCore/templates/&quot; + data[i].templateHtml ,function(html){&#xA;                            a[i]=html;&#xA;                        });&#xA;                    }&#xA;                }).then(function(d){&#xA;                    for (var j=0;j&amp;lt;data.length;j++)&#xA;                    {&#xA;&#xA;                        filterTemplate=Handlebars.compile(a[j]);&#xA;&#xA;                        replaceFilterTemplate(data[i].classids[j]);&#xA;&#xA;                    }&#xA;                })&#xA;&#xA;            }&#xA;        );&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2978398" LastActivityDate="2013-11-14T21:40:14.990" Title="javascript : Uncaught SyntaxError: Unexpected identifier" Tags="&lt;javascript&gt;&lt;jquery&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="37787510" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37783297" CreationDate="2016-06-13T10:35:13.000" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;QFileDialog.getOpenFileName()&lt;/code&gt; in PyQt5 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pyqt.sourceforge.net/Docs/PyQt5/pyqt4_differences.html#qfiledialog&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;is the same&lt;/a&gt; as &lt;a href=&quot;http://pyqt.sourceforge.net/Docs/PyQt4/qfiledialog.html#getOpenFileNameAndFilter&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;QFileDialog.getOpenFileNameAndFilter()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in PyQt4, it returns the file name and the filter selected by the user. You can use&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;file = QtWidgets.QFileDialog.getOpenFileName()[0]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to get only the file, or&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;file, filter = QtWidgets.QFileDialog.getOpenFileName()&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;which I find clearer because it's immediately obvious what the method returns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1350899" LastActivityDate="2016-06-13T10:35:13.000" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="6177129" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6177364" CreationDate="2011-05-30T13:46:59.763" Score="0" ViewCount="261" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a GWT application based on the MVP+App Controller Design. I also have a MySQL database as the back-end persistence storage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;strong&gt;shared&lt;/strong&gt; folder I have a *&lt;em&gt;Feed *&lt;/em&gt; model object. Feed objects are to be fetched as an ArrayList by my application(Imagining it to be a twitter like Application)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each Feed Model object in my Application can have an attached document with it. However it is optional. If the user requests for the attachment by clicking I would want to server the Attached document.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had in mind of keeping a Blob refrence as one of the Attribute of my Feed object. However GWT does not allow using Blob class for Client side code.(&lt;strong&gt;shared&lt;/strong&gt; folder is used by client as well as server side code)&#xA;Getting the attached documents for all the Feeds and passing around a byte of Array will take a lot of bandwidth. :|&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What can be a possible way around?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="220903" LastActivityDate="2011-05-30T14:10:38.950" Title="Model Object in GWT with Blob as an Attribute" Tags="&lt;mysql&gt;&lt;gwt&gt;&lt;download&gt;&lt;blob&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="8299557" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="8299615" CreationDate="2011-11-28T17:10:26.027" Score="-1" ViewCount="382" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unable to create a constant value of type 'Cllr.Domain.Business.Wort'.&#xA;Only primitive types ('such as Int32, String, and Guid') are supported in this context.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm having this bug on my code...i dont want to paste the code here cause it's a lot of code...and i myself cannot say where exactly the fault is.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so if any one here has this bug or can say what might cause this bug...i will be glad to read your line&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1069808" LastEditorUserId="270591" LastEditDate="2011-11-28T17:20:12.577" LastActivityDate="2011-11-28T17:20:12.577" Title="Unable to create a constant value of type" Tags="&lt;linq&gt;&lt;entity-framework&gt;&lt;linq-to-entities&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" ClosedDate="2011-11-28T23:42:10.910" />
  <row Id="28815792" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-03-02T17:22:36.727" Score="1" ViewCount="3474" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to route a file to HTTP file upload API via Apache Camel. But I'm getting following exception&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;org.apache.camel.InvalidPayloadException: No body available of type: java.io.InputStream but has value: org.apache.http.entity.mime.MultipartFormEntity@71ef4d4f of type: org.apache.http.entity.mime.MultipartFormEntity on: org.apache.camel.component.file.GenericFileMessage@7e693963. Caused by: No type converter available to convert from type: org.apache.http.entity.mime.MultipartFormEntity to the required type: java.io.InputStream with value org.apache.http.entity.mime.MultipartFormEntity@71ef4d4f. Exchange[org.apache.camel.component.file.GenericFileMessage@7e693963]. Caused by: [org.apache.camel.NoTypeConversionAvailableException - No type converter available to convert from type: org.apache.http.entity.mime.MultipartFormEntity to the required type: java.io.InputStream with value org.apache.http.entity.mime.MultipartFormEntity@71ef4d4f]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can anyone help here?&#xA;Following is what I tried so far&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My fileupload controller method mapped with the URL api/fileupload expects a &lt;code&gt;MultipartHttpServletRequest&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MyCamelRouter.java&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class MyCamelRouter extends RouteBuilder {&#xA;&#xA;@Override&#xA;public void configure() throws Exception {&#xA;    from(&quot;file:C:/src&quot;)&#xA;        .process(new MyProcessor())&#xA;        .log(&quot;POST ${header.CamelFileName} to /upload&quot;)&#xA;        .setHeader(Exchange.CONTENT_TYPE, constant(&quot;multipart/form-data&quot;))&#xA;        .setHeader(Exchange.HTTP_METHOD, constant(&quot;POST&quot;))&#xA;        .to(&quot;http:localhost:8080/sampleUploader/api/fileupload&quot;)&#xA;        .log(&quot;HTTP response status: ${header.CamelHttpResponseCode}&quot;)&#xA;        .log(LoggingLevel.DEBUG, &quot;HTTP response body:\n${body}&quot;);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;}&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and in MyProcessor.java&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class MyProcessor implements Processor {&#xA;    public void process(Exchange exchange) throws Exception {&#xA;&#xA;        File filetoUpload = exchange.getIn().getBody(File.class);&#xA;        String fileName = exchange.getIn().getHeader(Exchange.FILE_NAME, String.class);&#xA;&#xA;        MultipartEntityBuilder entity = MultipartEntityBuilder.create();&#xA;        entity.addTextBody(&quot;fileName&quot;, fileName);&#xA;        entity.addBinaryBody(&quot;file&quot;, new File(filePath));&#xA;&#xA;        exchange.getOut().setBody(entity.build());  &#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;}&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://hilton.org.uk/blog/camel-multipart-form-data&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; is the link I followed for this(Scala DSL)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3689988" LastActivityDate="2015-03-03T13:23:47.527" Title="Apache Camel multipart route" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;file-upload&gt;&lt;apache-camel&gt;&lt;multipartform-data&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="13181120" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="13180994" CreationDate="2012-11-01T16:13:16.573" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.charlesproxy.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Charles&lt;/a&gt; is a proxy tool that does a good job of sniffing and logging http/https requests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25650" LastActivityDate="2012-11-01T16:13:16.573" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="3700421" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2010-09-13T12:38:18.887" Score="1" ViewCount="375" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is this method right?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;switch ($_GET['get']){ &#xA;  case 'show':&#xA;        echo 'show';&#xA;  break;&#xA;&#xA;  case is_numeric($_GET['app']):&#xA;        echo $_GET['app'];&#xA;  break;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1377781" LastEditorUserId="1033581" LastEditDate="2017-08-27T03:26:35.400" LastActivityDate="2017-08-27T03:26:35.400" Title="PHP switch issue" Tags="&lt;php&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="28524156" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28524100" CreationDate="2015-02-15T08:09:21.220" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;snippet&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot; data-hide=&quot;false&quot;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div class=&quot;snippet-code&quot;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&quot;snippet-code-js lang-js prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$( document ).ready(function() {&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;$( &quot;#my_button&quot;).click(function() {&#xD;&#xA;    $(&quot;#main_section&quot;).html(&quot;this is the updated text&quot;); //the code that changes the content of the div&#xD;&#xA;    });&#xD;&#xA;    });&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&quot;snippet-code-html lang-html prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC &quot;-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN&quot; &quot;http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;html xmlns=&quot;http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;head&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;meta http-equiv=&quot;Content-Type&quot; content=&quot;text/html; charset=UTF-8&quot; /&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &amp;lt;script src=&quot;https://ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/2.1.3/jquery.min.js&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Untitled Document&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;/head&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;div id=&quot;book&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Price&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;  &amp;lt;div id=&quot;main_section&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;      &amp;lt;div id=&quot;tablef&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;          &amp;lt;div id=&quot;table&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;              &amp;lt;div id=&quot;cell&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Day Time Packages 9am-3pm&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;          &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;       &amp;lt;div id=&quot;table2&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;           &amp;lt;div id=&quot;cell2&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Night Time Packages 3pm-Late&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;       &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA; &amp;lt;div id=&quot;button_section&quot;&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA; &amp;lt;input type=&quot;button&quot;id=&quot;my_button&quot; value=&quot;Click me&quot;/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You just missed # sign in the jquery selector! &lt;strong&gt;($(&quot;#main_section&quot;))&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1505865" LastActivityDate="2015-02-15T08:09:21.220" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="32995322" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32995163" CreationDate="2015-10-07T14:43:29.260" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your interest in OpenMDAO.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The reason that the GUI will not start for you using 0.13.0 is that it was discontinued after 0.10.3.2, as noted here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://openmdao.org/openmdao-version-0-12-0/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://openmdao.org/openmdao-version-0-12-0/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The video is from 0.10.3.2 and is marked as &quot;out of date&quot; for that reason.  However, if you still want to try out the GUI, 0.10.3.2 is still available for download here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://openmdao.org/downloads/archive/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://openmdao.org/downloads/archive/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2308337" LastActivityDate="2015-10-07T14:43:29.260" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="20739493" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="20737426" CreationDate="2013-12-23T08:16:19.103" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have tested this myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default UIAlertview content is a textview. How large you are giving the content UIAlertview will definetly present it in a textview. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think you have given the text in Alertview title. You should have given it in the message.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/zyem4.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="404848" LastActivityDate="2013-12-23T08:16:19.103" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="31632416" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31585906" CreationDate="2015-07-26T00:29:39.853" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pypi.python.org/pypi/pixelscan/0.1.0&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is an implementation I wrote to scan a raster of points in a ring pattern. You can invoke the function using radii 0, 1, 2, etc, and it will give you the indices you want. You can then use those indices to access and print the element values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3833603" LastEditorUserId="3833603" LastEditDate="2015-08-08T00:43:42.713" LastActivityDate="2015-08-08T00:43:42.713" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="30984802" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30983866" CreationDate="2015-06-22T16:09:54.073" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you want to terminate the calculation at the time a warning is issued, you can use the &lt;code&gt;warnings&lt;/code&gt; module's ability to force certain types of warnings to be raised as exceptions. You can do this by writing:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;warnings.simplefilter('error')&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will turn &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; warnings into errors and immediately halt the program. The downside is that the computation cannot be resumed by simply catching the exception: it's done for good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you wish to &lt;em&gt;pause&lt;/em&gt; the program instead, you can use a little &quot;hack&quot; to override the function that the &lt;code&gt;warnings&lt;/code&gt; module uses to display warnings. Overriding this function is explicitly allowed by the documentation, though our present purpose differs from what the docs have in mind. Here's a simple warning handler that asks the user whether or not to continue. If the user says no, the error is promoted to an exception:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;def handle_warning(message, category, filename, lineno, file=None, line=None):&#xA;    print('A warning occurred:')&#xA;    print(message)&#xA;    print('Do you wish to continue?')&#xA;&#xA;    while True:&#xA;        response = input('y/n: ').lower()&#xA;        if response not in {'y', 'n'}:&#xA;            print('Not understood.')&#xA;        else:&#xA;            break&#xA;&#xA;    if response == 'n':&#xA;        raise category(message)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And we then override the default warning handler:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;warnings.showwarning = handle_warning&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now we try to optimize a flat function:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;from scipy.optimize import fsolve&#xA;fsolve(lambda x: 1, 1)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We almost immediately get a message:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;A warning occurred:&#xA;The iteration is not making good progress, as measured by the &#xA;  improvement from the last ten iterations.&#xA;Do you wish to continue?&#xA;y/n:&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If we answer &lt;code&gt;y&lt;/code&gt;, the optimization will be allowed to continue and return its result. If we answer &lt;code&gt;n&lt;/code&gt;, an exception is raised and the computation terminated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Context Manager Solution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, if you don't want to override the &lt;code&gt;showwarning&lt;/code&gt; function on the module level, you can use a context manager. We can place it inside a function that wraps everything up nice and neat:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;def pause_if_warning(function, *args, **kwargs):&#xA;    with warnings.catch_warnings():&#xA;        warnings.showwarning = handle_warning&#xA;        return function(*args, **kwargs)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So we can now write:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;pause_if_warning(fsolve, lambda x: 1, 1)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to get the same behavior as above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1231929" LastEditorUserId="1231929" LastEditDate="2015-06-22T16:25:40.657" LastActivityDate="2015-06-22T16:25:40.657" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="1481297" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="1482331" CreationDate="2009-09-26T14:08:04.267" Score="1" ViewCount="1826" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to add checkboxes to the leaf nodes in a TreeView in WPF. I know how to do this if we have a fixed number of levels in the hierarchy and using a HierarchicalDataTemplate for each level. But what to do when I want this:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;-Node 1&lt;br&gt;&#xA;-- Node 1a (leaf node with checkbox)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;-- Node 1b&lt;br&gt;&#xA;--- Node 1bI (leaf node with checkbox)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;-Node 2&lt;br&gt;&#xA;-- Node 2a (leaf node with checkbox)  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I set the DataContext in the code file to a DataTable. Just one table, with a relation to it self.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;DataContext = ds.MyDataTable;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;XAML:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;UserControl x:Class=&quot;JostyWpfControls.UserControl1&quot;&#xA;    xmlns=&quot;http://schemas.microsoft.com/winfx/2006/xaml/presentation&quot;&#xA;    xmlns:x=&quot;http://schemas.microsoft.com/winfx/2006/xaml&quot; &#xA;    Height=&quot;240&quot; Width=&quot;312&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;UserControl.Resources&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;HierarchicalDataTemplate x:Key=&quot;myTemplate&quot; &#xA;            ItemsSource=&quot;{Binding myDatasetRelation}&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;CheckBox IsChecked=&quot;{Binding IsChosen}&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;TextBlock Text=&quot;{Binding Description}&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;/CheckBox&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/HierarchicalDataTemplate&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/UserControl.Resources&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;Grid&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;TreeView x:Name=&quot;treeView&quot; &#xA;            ItemsSource=&quot;{Binding}&quot; &#xA;            ItemTemplate=&quot;{StaticResource myTemplate}&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/TreeView&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/Grid&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/UserControl&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is working, but gives me a chechbox to all nodes. I just want the leaf nodes to have a checkbox.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172696" LastEditorUserId="172696" LastEditDate="2009-09-26T18:20:14.697" LastActivityDate="2009-09-26T22:27:44.697" Title="Own template for leaf nodes in a WPF TreeView with unknown levels" Tags="&lt;wpf&gt;&lt;treeview&gt;&lt;hierarchicaldatatemplate&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="29297399" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-03-27T09:35:30.013" Score="0" ViewCount="273" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is the best practice to handle application's settings contains in the external INI file between several forms?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Suppose that I have two forms -- &lt;code&gt;MainForm&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;SettingsForm&lt;/code&gt;. User can open the &lt;code&gt;SettingsForm&lt;/code&gt; from the &lt;code&gt;MainForm&lt;/code&gt;. Now I have smth like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On &lt;code&gt;Load&lt;/code&gt; event of the &lt;code&gt;SettingsForm&lt;/code&gt; I read application's settings from the file and change the UI appropriately&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On &quot;Save&quot; button press I write new options' values to the file&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the &quot;SettingsFormClosed&quot; event of the &lt;code&gt;MainForm&lt;/code&gt; I read the settings from the file again&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think that the last thing is the most terrible in this case. Maybe I should use smth like &lt;code&gt;SettingsSingleton&lt;/code&gt; or smth like this? What is the best practice to do it in C# and Windows Forms?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1608835" LastActivityDate="2015-03-27T10:04:16.823" Title="What is the best practice to handle application's settings between several forms" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;winforms&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="26590412" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26590122" CreationDate="2014-10-27T14:57:12.327" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;This part of the code:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$condition=$column.'='.self::PARAM_PREFIX.self::$paramCount;&#xA;$this-&amp;gt;params[self::PARAM_PREFIX.self::$paramCount++]=$value;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seems to be for storing parametrized values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then in a Query Builder, it will use them as numerated parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do that way in a script I made myself, I really doubt Qian (or whatever) would miss it and leave a code injection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, DID YOU TEST IT? You could add random SQL and see if it gets escaped.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1335189" LastActivityDate="2014-10-27T14:57:12.327" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="25664754" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25663525" CreationDate="2014-09-04T11:50:56.353" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;None of the code examples here actually implement the decorator pattern (well, they didn't when I wrote this...). It defeats the point if the concrete classes and decorators are part of the same inheritance tree. In that case there would be no point to actually store a reference to a concrete object, because you could simply call &lt;code&gt;base&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the decorator pattern, your concrete classes and decorators should implement a common interface. It doesn't rely on inheritance nor polymorphism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public interface IComponent&#xA;{&#xA;    String getComputer();&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;public class Computer : IComponent&#xA;{&#xA;    public String getComputer()&#xA;    {&#xA;        return &quot;computer&quot;;&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;public abstract class ComponentDecorator&#xA;{&#xA;    protected ComponentDecorator(IComponent component)&#xA;    {&#xA;        this.Component = component;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    protected IComponent Component { get; private set; }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;public class Disk : ComponentDecorator, IComponent&#xA;{&#xA;    public Disk(IComponent c) : base(c)&#xA;    {&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public String getComputer()&#xA;    {&#xA;        return this.Component.getComputer() + &quot; and a disk&quot;;&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;public class Monitor : ComponentDecorator, IComponent&#xA;{&#xA;    public Monitor(IComponent c)&#xA;        : base(c)&#xA;    {&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public String getComputer()&#xA;    {&#xA;        return this.Component.getComputer() + &quot; and a monitor&quot;;&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;class Program&#xA;{&#xA;    static void Main(string[] args)&#xA;    {&#xA;        IComponent computer = new Monitor(new Disk(new Computer()));&#xA;&#xA;        Console.WriteLine(&quot; You are getting a &quot; + computer.getComputer());&#xA;        Console.ReadKey();&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I extracted an interface. You could use an abstract class all the same, though. The abstract decorator is simply to re-use storing the component reference, but nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point is that the decorators shouldn't inherit from the concrete class(es), because that would defeat the point of the decorator pattern. As you can see, I didn't even make the base decorator implement the interface to demonstrate that you need absolutely no late binding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;BTW: &lt;code&gt;getComputer()&lt;/code&gt; violates the C# conventions. It should be a property in C# and start with a capital letter. Apart from language-specific conventions, the name of the method is lying about its intention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2617720" LastActivityDate="2014-09-04T11:50:56.353" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="31532065" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31531998" CreationDate="2015-07-21T06:45:22.597" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;dr(&quot;img&quot;)&lt;/code&gt; returns either &lt;code&gt;DBNull.Value&lt;/code&gt;, or a &lt;code&gt;byte[]&lt;/code&gt;. You can use the stream overload of the &lt;code&gt;Bitmap&lt;/code&gt; constructor to load this. In C# (should be easy to translate to VB), you can do it like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;var imageData = (byte[])dr[&quot;img&quot;];&#xA;&#xA;using (var ms = new MemoryStream(imageData))&#xA;{&#xA;  var bmp = new Bitmap(ms);&#xA;&#xA;  // Work with bmp&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As Mark correctly noted, you're supposed to keep the stream open for the whole life-time of the &lt;code&gt;Bitmap&lt;/code&gt; - this is actually a bit trickier than it seems, because the &lt;code&gt;Bitmap&lt;/code&gt; doesn't even keep a reference to the stream.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The easiest way to handle this is to clone the bitmap after you create it, to remove the dependency on the stream. Unless you can do whatever work  you need to do within the &lt;code&gt;using&lt;/code&gt; - unlikely if you want to display it in a &lt;code&gt;PictureBox&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also use &lt;code&gt;ImageConverter.ConvertFrom&lt;/code&gt; directly, but all it does is create the &lt;code&gt;MemoryStream&lt;/code&gt; if used on raw &lt;code&gt;byte[]&lt;/code&gt; data :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3032289" LastEditorUserId="3032289" LastEditDate="2015-07-21T15:11:59.057" LastActivityDate="2015-07-21T15:11:59.057" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="11222219" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11222069" CreationDate="2012-06-27T08:29:05.537" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's because you're using &lt;code&gt;+&lt;/code&gt; for concatenation rather than &lt;code&gt;.&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$output .= '{&quot;category&quot;: &quot;' . $result-&amp;gt;Category . '&quot;,';&#xA;$output .= '&quot;title&quot;: &quot;' . $result-&amp;gt;Title . '&quot;,';&#xA;$output .= '&quot;price&quot;: &quot;' . $result-&amp;gt;Price . '&quot;,';&#xA;$output .= '},';&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But you should really not construct the JSON yourself, as it leads to a number of errors making for invalid JSON (trailing commas etc). Use something like this instead:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static function printJson(array $arrayOfResults)&#xA;{&#xA;    $results['results'] = array_map('get_object_vars', $arrayOfResults);&#xA;&#xA;    return json_encode($results);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="283078" LastEditorUserId="367456" LastEditDate="2012-06-27T11:03:48.443" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T11:03:48.443" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="40090220" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="20938358" CreationDate="2016-10-17T15:25:01.710" Score="0" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class Euler2 {&#xA;public static void main(String[] args) {&#xA;    int fibonacci;&#xA;    int num = 0;&#xA;    int num2 = 1;&#xA;    int loop;&#xA;    int sum = 0;&#xA;    System.out.println(num2);&#xA;        for (loop = 0; loop &amp;lt;= 32; loop++) {&#xA;            fibonacci = num + num2;&#xA;            num = num2;&#xA;            num2 = fibonacci;&#xA;            System.out.println(&quot;Fibonacci number : &quot; + fibonacci);&#xA;        sum += fibonacci;&#xA;        System.out.println(&quot;This is the sum &quot; +sum);&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;}&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I solved it like this, it's a little more efficient and the math works but Euler hates me, hope this helps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7031860" LastActivityDate="2016-10-17T15:25:01.710" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="18345584" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-08-20T21:53:10.683" Score="0" ViewCount="188" Body="&lt;p&gt;In a repository with two branches (master &amp;amp; develop) and a git subtree repository included in folder &lt;code&gt;shared&lt;/code&gt;, is it possible to automatically synch the &lt;code&gt;shared&lt;/code&gt; subtree to a specific version (commit) when changing branches?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My best guess is that I'm probably looking for a way to run a script whenever I change branches locally. The script then performs the necessary git pull/fetch commands on the subtree.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let's say the master branch should always point to v1.0 tagged commit of the shared subtree repository, while the develop branch always checks out the latest commit. Edits to the shared subtree are only made in the develop branch and will be committed (or stashed) before switching to master.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="201863" LastEditorUserId="201863" LastEditDate="2013-08-20T21:58:45.537" LastActivityDate="2014-10-21T12:40:23.403" Title="Git: possible to point subtree to different commits when switching branches?" Tags="&lt;git&gt;&lt;github&gt;&lt;git-branch&gt;&lt;git-subtree&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="25833700" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2014-09-14T13:22:24.657" Score="0" ViewCount="430" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to do a game in which i have to rotate a bitmap multiple times.But sometimes it shows Out Of Memory Error.How to solve this? Can anyone suggest me a way to recycle a bitmap or any other way out. This is the code I have written :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;       public void rotate() {&#xA;         CustomImageView customImageView=this;&#xA;        Bitmap bitmap = ((BitmapDrawable)customImageView.getDrawable()).getBitmap();&#xA;        Matrix matrix = new Matrix();&#xA;        matrix.setRotate(90, (float) bitmap.getWidth() / 2, (float) bitmap.getHeight() / 2);&#xA;        try {&#xA;            Bitmap b2 = Bitmap.createBitmap(bitmap, 0, 0, bitmap.getWidth(), bitmap.getHeight(), matrix, true);&#xA;            if (bitmap != b2) {&#xA;                bitmap.recycle();&#xA;                bitmap = b2;&#xA;            }&#xA;        } catch (OutOfMemoryError ex) {&#xA;        System.out.println(&quot;Exception::out of memory in customimage&quot;);&#xA;        throw ex;&#xA;        }&#xA;        customImageView.setImageBitmap(bitmap);&#xA;      }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2659731" LastEditorUserId="4014448" LastEditDate="2014-09-14T13:25:04.620" LastActivityDate="2014-09-14T13:40:18.497" Title="Memory Error While Rotating An Image" Tags="&lt;android&gt;&lt;out-of-memory&gt;&lt;bitmapimage&gt;&lt;recycle&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="5483180" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5483103" CreationDate="2011-03-30T07:21:50.390" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You question is very broad but you could take a look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://java-source.net/open-source/chat-servers&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://java-source.net/open-source/chat-servers&lt;/a&gt; for Open-Source Chat Servers written in Java. But these are actual servers that run and clients connect to. As you mentioned a domain-name you might want a Web Based Chat Solution, check out - &lt;a href=&quot;http://chipchat.sourceforge.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://chipchat.sourceforge.net/&lt;/a&gt; - for this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Update Users want a Web Based solution using a Comet Approach&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe try - &lt;a href=&quot;http://avricot.com/blog/index.php?post/2009/05/19/AvriChat-%3A-Real-time-Chat-Javascript-Comet-and-Java-Server&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://avricot.com/blog/index.php?post/2009/05/19/AvriChat-%3A-Real-time-Chat-Javascript-Comet-and-Java-Server&lt;/a&gt; or - &lt;a href=&quot;http://cometdaily.com/2009/10/23/concrete-comet-examples/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://cometdaily.com/2009/10/23/concrete-comet-examples/&lt;/a&gt; also shows a example of chat with comment&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please try Google it has all the information you will ever need.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="657852" LastEditorUserId="657852" LastEditDate="2011-03-30T07:44:37.633" LastActivityDate="2011-03-30T07:44:37.633" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="15683913" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="15683238" CreationDate="2013-03-28T14:04:10.677" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you're having trouble with StringBuffers, you can try a simple approach with a string array, something like this :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String str[]= new String[0];&#xA;str[0]=&quot;0&quot;;             &#xA;mCursor= db.rawQuery(Query, null);                      &#xA;if (mCursor.moveToNext()) {         &#xA;str[0]=mCursor.getString(0);&#xA;System.out.println(&quot;**************&quot;+str[0]);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1436281" LastActivityDate="2013-03-28T14:04:10.677" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="37697387" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37696035" CreationDate="2016-06-08T08:39:37.330" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexdocs.pm/ecto/Ecto.Repo.html#c:insert_or_update/2&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;Ecto.Repo.insert_or_update/2&lt;/a&gt;, please note that for this to work, you will have to load existing models from the database.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt; model = %Post{id: 'existing_id', ...}&#xA; MyRepo.insert_or_update changeset&#xA; # =&amp;gt; {:error, &quot;id already exists&quot;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;result =&#xA;  case MyRepo.get(Post, id) do&#xA;    nil  -&amp;gt; %Post{id: id} # Post not found, we build one&#xA;    post -&amp;gt; post          # Post exists, let's use it&#xA;  end&#xA;  |&amp;gt; Post.changeset(changes)&#xA;  |&amp;gt; MyRepo.insert_or_update&#xA;&#xA;case result do&#xA;  {:ok, model}        -&amp;gt; # Inserted or updated with success&#xA;  {:error, changeset} -&amp;gt; # Something went wrong&#xA;end&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2097420" LastActivityDate="2016-06-08T08:39:37.330" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="29961703" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="29608537" CreationDate="2015-04-30T07:32:56.900" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;If I understand correctly, the issue is about re-validating files after changing dependencies. &#xA;1. It is not related to indexer (it just records that a file contains some elements) &#xA;2. It is not related to parser (which produces AST). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It should happen in a builder. You could try DLTK support for that by implementing IBuildParticipant or IScriptBuilder.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="826958" LastActivityDate="2015-04-30T07:32:56.900" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="11174794" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-24T03:44:07.230" Score="0" ViewCount="627" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to know if it is possible to get the current location of mobile phone using mobile number . Can you suggest me any algorithm. I want to create a web service and integrate it with Google maps. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1354304" LastActivityDate="2012-06-24T04:37:18.317" Title="Mobile locator using cellphone number?" Tags="&lt;web-services&gt;&lt;algorithm&gt;&lt;mobile&gt;&lt;gps&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="44634060" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44632375" CreationDate="2017-06-19T15:07:28.977" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've tried changing the encoding but, still the same issue is happening.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally I decided to set the strings in base64 format and then decode the strings in the build.gradle like this&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;resValue 'string', 'APP_NAME_JA', new String(APP_NAME_JA.decodeBase64(), &quot;UTF-8&quot;)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1894850" LastActivityDate="2017-06-19T15:07:28.977" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="8866617" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="8866664" CreationDate="2012-01-15T00:32:46.307" Score="1" ViewCount="8540" Body="&lt;p&gt;I try to retrieve a array from one table What is wrong with this code?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$_fbexclude = mysql_query(&quot;SELECT fbempfang FROM fbinvite WHERE fbreturn = '1' &quot;);&#xA;$fbexcludearray= mysql_fetch_array($_fbexclude);&#xA;&#xA;// Convert the array &#xA;$excludes = implode(',', $fbexcludearray);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;code&gt;echo $excludes;&lt;/code&gt; It only gives me just the following response: &lt;code&gt;1000033xxx161,1000033xxx161&lt;/code&gt; Twice the same fbempfang&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1107573" LastActivityDate="2014-06-03T09:20:07.713" Title="mysql query and implode" Tags="&lt;php&gt;&lt;mysql&gt;&lt;arrays&gt;&lt;facebook&gt;&lt;implode&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="14093408" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="14093520" CreationDate="2012-12-30T18:33:32.783" Score="1" ViewCount="218" Body="&lt;p&gt;as my project gets a little over loaded with &lt;code&gt;javascript&lt;/code&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;code&gt;jQuery&lt;/code&gt; scripts, &#xA;i am having problems with my try on separating it all to sections, ...like  into &lt;em&gt;categories&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;stages&lt;/em&gt; ...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so &lt;strong&gt;before&lt;/strong&gt; these two calls,  which are 'current project' calls , &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA; &lt;pre class=&quot;lang-aspx prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;head&amp;gt;&#xA;    //i am loading the jQuery &amp;amp; jQuery-UI... and then :&#xA;&#xA;    // right after jQuery comes my first section of project&#xA;    &amp;lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;jsV2\jQueryAjaxNoPostBack.js&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;jsV2\stage1.js&quot; &amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;            // is valid in stage1.js , naturally...&#xA;            var jsTxtVal = document.getElementById(&quot;TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;            //and that won't work&#xA;            var jQueryTxtVal= $('#TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage').val();&#xA;    &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/head&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and in that separated file i try &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA; &lt;pre class=&quot;lang-jquery prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;//stage1.js&#xA;&#xA;//---- before ready()-------&#xA;//won't work&#xA;var jQueryTxtVal= $('#TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage').val();&#xA;&#xA;//works &#xA;var jsTxtVal = document.getElementById(&quot;TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;$('document').ready(function () {&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;var TBX_TableSel = $('#TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage');&#xA;var jQueryTxtVal= $('#TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage').val();&#xA;var jsTxtVal = document.getElementById(&quot;TBX_TableSelectorFirstStage&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;$('.someElement's Class).click(function () {&#xA;&#xA;    // this will not work unless i will assign &quot;jQueryTxtVal&quot; right here .&#xA;&#xA;    alert(jQueryTxtVal);&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;   //and... this will work no matter where the assignment took place .&#xA;   //either in main page (i call it &quot;the globlas&quot; of project)&#xA;   //or at the top of every &quot;section&quot; of project...&#xA;&#xA;    alert(jsTxtVal );&#xA;&#xA;   });&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;now if I would use  &lt;em&gt;plain&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;code&gt;JavaScript&lt;/code&gt; ,  I could even put a section of global variables, for all methods... almost anywhere , like within a &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;sctipt&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/srctipt&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; under jquery, in main page &lt;code&gt;.aspx&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so I would like to know , &lt;strong&gt;how could i use &quot;globals&quot; in jQuery ?&lt;/strong&gt; &#xA;or it just the use case for that(?) .. I wouldn't think so...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;...I also tried &lt;code&gt;defer=&quot;defer&quot;&lt;/code&gt; on &lt;code&gt;stage1.js&lt;/code&gt; call , inside head- main page &lt;code&gt;.aspx&lt;/code&gt;&#xA;nothing I try succeeds&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1329184" LastActivityDate="2012-12-30T18:47:15.187" Title="javascript vs jQuery custom/Global Variables scope" Tags="&lt;javascript&gt;&lt;jquery&gt;&lt;asp.net&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="34059485" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="34060362" CreationDate="2015-12-03T06:47:21.070" Score="0" ViewCount="51" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have String[ ]Result as a result from my project. So, the String length is unstable, depend on the input. So, how can I show this string result with android text view. For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    String[]Mypermission = {............};&#xA;    String[]permissions = {......input......}  //input array&#xA;    String[]Result = null;&#xA;    for(int i=0; i&amp;lt;Mypermission.length; i++)&#xA;    {&#xA;       for(int j=0; j&amp;lt;permissions.length; j++)&#xA;       {&#xA;           if(Mypermission[i].equals(permissions[j].substring(permissions[j].lastIndexOf(&quot;.&quot;))))&#xA;           { int k=0; Result[k]= Mypermission[i]; k++;}&#xA;       }&#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can't think off how to write the result_xml layout. Thank you everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="5586163" LastActivityDate="2015-12-03T12:13:23.473" Title="How to show String result in android text view from unpredictable String[ ] length?" Tags="&lt;android&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" ClosedDate="2015-12-03T09:41:31.160" />
  <row Id="32260612" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-27T22:45:26.637" Score="0" ViewCount="358" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am loading files into Redshift with the COPY command using a manifest. The files are in S3. Unfortunately, there's about 2,000 files per table, so it's like&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;users1.csv.gz, users2.csv.gz, users3.csv.gz, users4.csv.gz, etc&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't know if that matters or not, because the files are loaded with a manifest, and the manifest is supposed to parallelize this. That being said, it is really slow to load a table, and I need to speed it up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What are some things I could do to speed this up?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3011531" LastActivityDate="2016-11-22T11:17:35.213" Title="Speeding up Redshift COPY loading" Tags="&lt;performance&gt;&lt;optimization&gt;&lt;amazon-redshift&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="5023068" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="5023114" CreationDate="2011-02-16T22:41:34.783" Score="-1" ViewCount="123" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Possible Duplicate:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/139157/what-is-the-best-way-to-prevent-highlighting-of-text-when-clicking-on-its-contain&quot;&gt;What is the best way to prevent highlighting of text when clicking on its containing div in javascript?&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When a user clicks and drags how do you stop firefox from highlighting your content?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198034" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T12:13:17.217" LastActivityDate="2011-02-16T23:52:03.260" Title="stopping firefox from selecting content on webpage" Tags="&lt;javascript&gt;&lt;firefox&gt;&lt;highlighting&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" ClosedDate="2011-02-17T00:37:17.183" />
  <row Id="931663" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="931536" CreationDate="2009-05-31T08:47:09.030" Score="16" Body="&lt;p&gt;It may help if you post a test section of minimal code needed to reproduce the problem.  I tested the following code on Windows and a Linux system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class Main {&#xA;&#xA;    /**&#xA;     * @param args the command line arguments&#xA;     */&#xA;    public static void main(String[] args) throws Exception {&#xA;        Runtime.getRuntime().exec(args[0]);&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And tested with the following on Linux:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;java -jar JustForTesting.jar /home/monceaux/Desktop/__TMP/test.sh&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;where test.sh looks like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#!/bin/bash&#xA;ping -i 20 localhost&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;as well as this on Linux:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;java -jar JustForTesting.jar gedit&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And tested this on Windows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;java -jar JustForTesting.jar notepad.exe&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of these launched their intended programs, but the Java application had no problems exiting.  I have the following versions of Sun's JVM as reported by &lt;code&gt;java -version&lt;/code&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Windows:  1.6.0_13-b03&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Linux:    1.6.0_10-b33&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have not had a chance to test on my Mac yet.  Perhaps there is some interaction occuring with other code in your project that may not be clear.  You may want to try this test app and see what the results are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="111256" LastEditorUserId="5091346" LastEditDate="2017-07-04T06:06:59.953" LastActivityDate="2017-07-04T06:06:59.953" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="19527762" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18233059" CreationDate="2013-10-22T20:33:21.327" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;This explains the differences nicely:&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.msdn.com/b/alexj/archive/2012/08/15/odata-support-in-asp-net-web-api.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://blogs.msdn.com/b/alexj/archive/2012/08/15/odata-support-in-asp-net-web-api.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="222748" LastActivityDate="2013-10-22T20:33:21.327" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="20523915" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="20500220" CreationDate="2013-12-11T15:59:38.370" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;After looking more closer &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/11451617/names-not-displayed-on-retrieving-sms-details?answertab=votes#tab-top&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; example actually helped me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1897222" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T10:25:00.900" LastActivityDate="2013-12-11T15:59:38.370" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="39009407" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="38996647" CreationDate="2016-08-18T03:12:00.220" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;You have 3 issues with your route definitions&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Only the last parameter in a route definition can be marked with&#xA;&lt;code&gt;UrlParameter.Optional&lt;/code&gt;. If you were to provide only one, then the&#xA;routing engine has no way of knowing which parameter should be bound&#xA;so the value(s) would be added as query string parameters).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The main issue however is the order of the routes. The routing&lt;br&gt;&#xA;engines searches the definitions in the order they are declared and &#xA;stops as soon as it finds a matching one, and in your case the&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;code&gt;IDRoute&lt;/code&gt; will match so the routes need to be swapped.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;That alone however may cause issues with other route definitions, so&#xA;its best to make your route uniquely identifiable, for example by&#xA;specifying the controller name in the route definition.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your definitions should be&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static void RegisterRoutes(RouteCollection routes)&#xA;{&#xA;    routes.IgnoreRoute(&quot;{resource}.axd/{*pathInfo}&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;    routes.MapRoute(&#xA;        name: &quot;ProcessRoute&quot;,&#xA;        url: &quot;InspectionTemplate/{action}/{id}/{processId}&quot;,&#xA;        defaults: new { controller = &quot;InspectionTemplate&quot;, action = &quot;TemplateBuilder&quot;, processId = UrlParameter.Optional }&#xA;    );&#xA;&#xA;    routes.MapRoute(&#xA;        name: &quot;DateRoute&quot;,&#xA;        url: &quot;Inspection/{action}/{year}/{month}/{day}&quot;,&#xA;        defaults: new { controller = &quot;Inspection&quot;, action = &quot;Assign&quot;, } // assumes all parameters are required&#xA;    );&#xA;&#xA;    // The default will only be match if the url does not start with '/InspectionTemplate/' or '/Inspection/'&#xA;    routes.MapRoute(&#xA;        name: &quot;IDRoute&quot;,&#xA;        url: &quot;{controller}/{action}/{id}&quot;,&#xA;        defaults: new { controller = &quot;Login&quot;, action = &quot;Index&quot;, id = UrlParameter.Optional }&#xA;    );&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3559349" LastActivityDate="2016-08-18T03:12:00.220" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="13721851" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-12-05T11:05:46.077" Score="2" ViewCount="594" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to make a call directly like this&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String url = &quot;tel:&quot; +&quot;029870125,198#&quot;;                              &#xA;Intent intent = new Intent(Intent.ACTION_CALL,Uri.parse(url));&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but the problem is that Android is sending &lt;code&gt;198&lt;/code&gt; as &lt;code&gt;dtmf&lt;/code&gt;, but the &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; is not being sent. Is there any special mechanism needed to send &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; as &lt;code&gt;dtmf&lt;/code&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1878801" LastEditorUserId="1728642" LastEditDate="2012-12-05T11:29:48.483" LastActivityDate="2013-03-12T09:47:35.377" Title="Sending # as dtmf in android" Tags="&lt;android&gt;&lt;dtmf&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="711865" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="711807" CreationDate="2009-04-02T22:25:29.867" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Either this is really misstated or I'm just not getting something:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The application requests the web page and gets it and has to ascertain if it is another &quot;True&quot; or &quot;False&quot;, right?  This is to say that part of the web request isn't to return the true or false at the beginning which is where my first confusion is.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, why aren't you doing a similar comparison on the false cases and seeing if there are sufficient similarities to create 3 buckets of results for some random page requested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1) Page is more similar to true and thus is viewed as true.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2) Page is more similar to false and thus is viewed as false.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3) Page isn't more similar to either and thus the result is something like a null or exception situation as it isn't possible to discern which result makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example of where that 3rd case could happen:&#xA;Suppose the page contains an integer and if positive the result is true and if negative the result is false.  What if the result is 0?  Does 0 count as positive since it is equal to its absolute value or does it count as a negative for some reason?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or am I way off in what you are trying to do here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8745" OwnerDisplayName="JB King" LastActivityDate="2009-04-02T22:25:29.867" CommentCount="3" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-04-02T22:25:29.850" />
  <row Id="13532965" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-11-23T16:42:55.430" Score="0" ViewCount="4264" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;void findWay(int column,int sum,char *array,int s,stack_t sta)&#xA;{&#xA; if(array[s+column+2]=='0')&#xA;{&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I debug program, I am getting an error which is &quot;Address 0x53 out of bounds&quot; (if(maze[s+column+2]=='0') at this line). Why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Someone please help me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1848043" LastEditorUserId="1488917" LastEditDate="2012-11-23T16:48:23.797" LastActivityDate="2012-11-23T17:01:59.770" Title="C &lt;Address 0x53 out of bounds&gt; error" Tags="&lt;c&gt;&lt;indexoutofboundsexception&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="20231370" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="17602291" CreationDate="2013-11-27T01:35:08.060" Score="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can do this with an inline SVG background, using only CSS and no javascript.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&quot;lang-css prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;.background {&#xA;   // Draw an SVG top left to bottom right &#xA;   background: url(&quot;data:image/svg+xml;utf8,&amp;lt;svg xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg' version='1.1' preserveAspectRatio='none' viewBox='0 0 10 10'&amp;gt; &amp;lt;path d='M0 0 L0 10 L10 10' fill='red' /&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/svg&amp;gt;&quot;);&#xA;   background-repeat:no-repeat;&#xA;   background-position:center center;&#xA;   //scale it &#xA;   background-size: 100% 100%, auto;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See my fiddle:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jsfiddle.net/3GWw2/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://jsfiddle.net/3GWw2/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="111408" LastEditorUserId="11683" LastEditDate="2016-12-08T11:48:57.127" LastActivityDate="2016-12-08T11:48:57.127" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="21617130" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="21617035" CreationDate="2014-02-07T00:39:22.397" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If your some reason you absolutely had to reuse that terminal you could tell rails to daemonize by running:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;rails server -d&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's a little more tricky to stop but &lt;code&gt;kill $(lsof -i :3000 -t)&lt;/code&gt; may do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1198440" LastActivityDate="2014-02-07T00:39:22.397" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="45736724" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45735654" CreationDate="2017-08-17T13:39:36.090" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;The act of merging does several things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, the obvious: By default it applies the textual changes from (in this case) the hotfix to (in this case) the dev branch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, as you allude, it helps git understand that the changes that were made by (in this case) the hotfix are accounted for in (in this case) the dev branch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But maybe the most important thing it does: it puts the code changes made on the hotfix (since the hitfix/dev merge base) side-by-side with the changes made on dev (since the merge base) and provides an opportunity to review the results and &lt;em&gt;ensure&lt;/em&gt; that the changes made in the hotfix &lt;em&gt;really are in fact accounted for&lt;/em&gt; on dev.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think of this last point as the logical merge operation, whereas the mixing of textual changes is just one physical operation that &lt;em&gt;typically&lt;/em&gt; accomplishes that task.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, you object that if the merge is unnecessary, and someone resolves the merge incorrectly, this can introduce new bugs.  Well, ok... but here's another way to look at it.  Analyzing the changes in dev and the changes in the hotfix, and deciding that no physical merge is necessary, is just another strategy for performing the logical merge.  And, because your analysis &lt;em&gt;might not take everything into account&lt;/em&gt;, this strategy also might admit bugs.  (And those are likely to be embarrassing bugs because you already fixed them.)  And beyond that it has two disadvantages compared to doing the physical merge:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First (again as you note) it doesn't give git a way to know that the hotfix is accounted for in dev.  Merging the hotfix into dev has documentary value, even if you perform the merge using the &lt;code&gt;ours&lt;/code&gt; strategy (i.e. ignoring the hotfix altogether).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, the merge into dev has implications for testing.  A hotfix by its nature &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; introduce at least one new test case.  That should be merged into your codebase even if none of the production code from the hotfix is still relevant.  (And if refactoring changes how the test case needs to be written, that's part of the merge.)  Moreover, the merge commit needs to be run through the full test suite (which should also negate any concern that poor merge work would introduce bugs at this point).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bottom line is, if your testing is loose enough to falsify any part of what I just said, then worrying about how best to merge hotfixes is just arguing about what color to make the deck chairs on the Titanic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The last potential objection I can think of would be the so-called &quot;evil merge&quot;.  If &lt;em&gt;somehow&lt;/em&gt; a hotfix is obviated by later changes to dev &lt;em&gt;and yet a default merge would successfully auto-resolve&lt;/em&gt; (which I find highly unlikely, but for the sake of argument...), then producing a non-default merge (by using a strategy like &lt;code&gt;ours&lt;/code&gt;, or by amending the merge commit, or by using &lt;code&gt;--no-commit&lt;/code&gt;, ...) can cause trouble down the line with some operations.  The biggest concern would be rebasing, and in this context I don't think that's likely to be an issue.  But if it worries you, you could always complete the auto-merge and then use a subsequent commit to apply the &quot;correct&quot; merged state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7050130" LastActivityDate="2017-08-17T13:39:36.090" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="31331442" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31331310" CreationDate="2015-07-10T02:23:16.933" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am not too familiar with an edge list, but it looks like all you are doing is chaining the item column of the raw data frame into rows of a new data frame. For the edge list you could try to iterate through the item column and write each element of the link into new rows of the new data frame. Maybe a nested for loop for iterating would work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the co-occurence matrix, you could use pandas.cut to bin the data and obtain a frequency distribution list of each items co-occurence. Then you populate an array with each frequency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I haven't used pandas in a while, but I will see what I can do about a code solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3930079" LastActivityDate="2015-07-10T02:23:16.933" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="19469451" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19469278" CreationDate="2013-10-19T18:21:13.950" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;add this to your handler if you need a new page..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;window.open('url', 'window name', 'window settings');&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;or this if you want to redirect the actual view&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;window.location.href('url');&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;furthermore this should be a better choice:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$('div[id^=tabStrip-tab]').bind(&quot;click mouseover mouseout&quot;, handleEvent);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;now only the 'tabStrip-*' ids will trigger the events/handler&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1571383" LastEditorUserId="1571383" LastEditDate="2013-10-19T18:28:11.797" LastActivityDate="2013-10-19T18:28:11.797" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="17121004" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1011812" CreationDate="2013-06-15T06:50:54.730" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you are concerned more about the data rather than its formatting, then I suggest you to go with tweaking &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sqlite.org/download.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;the SQL source&lt;/a&gt;, its fully C based. Its really a painful process. As Afit said you will endup junks in between the valid chars.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2398604" LastActivityDate="2013-06-15T06:50:54.730" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="12037604" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="12037619" CreationDate="2012-08-20T12:25:36.090" Score="7" ViewCount="4994" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a question about enum variable in c++:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;type enmu {&#xA;   DAY1 = 1,&#xA;   DAY2,&#xA;   DAY3,&#xA;   DAY4&#xA;} DAYS;&#xA;&#xA;void main() {&#xA;   DAYS days;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;then what is the default value of days?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="user707549" LastActivityDate="2012-08-20T12:39:45.227" Title="what is the default value of enum variable?" Tags="&lt;c++&gt;&lt;c&gt;&lt;enums&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="38236026" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="38235785" CreationDate="2016-07-07T00:46:22.057" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I get a javascript error: &lt;code&gt;Uncaught TypeError: Cannot read property 'setCenter' of undefined&lt;/code&gt; on this line:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;map.setCenter(results[0].geometry.location);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main issue is the comma at the end of the definition of the &lt;code&gt;mapOptions&lt;/code&gt; variable, that makes the following declaration of the &lt;code&gt;map&lt;/code&gt; variable local to the &lt;code&gt;initialize_map&lt;/code&gt; function, make the line in &lt;code&gt;initialize_map&lt;/code&gt; initialize the global &lt;code&gt;map&lt;/code&gt; by changing that to a semi-colon (&lt;code&gt;;&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jsfiddle.net/geocodezip/313ksgh5/2/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;proof of concept fiddle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;code snippet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;snippet&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot; data-hide=&quot;false&quot; data-console=&quot;true&quot; data-babel=&quot;false&quot;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div class=&quot;snippet-code&quot;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&quot;snippet-code-js lang-js prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;// var marker = &amp;lt;?php echo json_encode($marker_img); ?&amp;gt;; //this should send the marker image url&#xD;&#xA;var latitude = '40.7127837'; //this is the latitude&#xD;&#xA;var longitude = '-74.0059413'; //this is the long&#xD;&#xA;var paddress = 'New York, NY'; //this is the address name&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;var geocoder;&#xD;&#xA;var map;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;function initialize_map() {&#xD;&#xA;  geocoder = new google.maps.Geocoder();&#xD;&#xA;  var latlng = new google.maps.LatLng(latitude, longitude);&#xD;&#xA;  var myOptions = {&#xD;&#xA;    scrollwheel: false,&#xD;&#xA;    zoom: 10,&#xD;&#xA;    center: latlng,&#xD;&#xA;    mapTypeId: google.maps.MapTypeId.ROADMAP,&#xD;&#xA;    styles: [{&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;administrative&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;all&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;visibility&quot;: &quot;on&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: 33&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;administrative&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;administrative&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;gamma&quot;: &quot;0.75&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;administrative.neighborhood&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text.fill&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-37&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;landscape&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;color&quot;: &quot;#f9f9f9&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;landscape.man_made&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;40&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;visibility&quot;: &quot;off&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;landscape.natural&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text.fill&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-37&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;landscape.natural&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text.stroke&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;weight&quot;: &quot;2&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;landscape.natural&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.icon&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;poi&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;80&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;poi&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;0&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;poi.attraction&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-4&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;poi.park&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;color&quot;: &quot;#c5dac6&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;visibility&quot;: &quot;on&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-95&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;62&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;poi.park&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;visibility&quot;: &quot;on&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: 20&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;all&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: 20&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;gamma&quot;: &quot;1.00&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;gamma&quot;: &quot;0.50&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.icon&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;gamma&quot;: &quot;0.50&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.highway&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;color&quot;: &quot;#c5c6c6&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.highway&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry.stroke&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-13&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.highway&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.icon&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;0&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;gamma&quot;: &quot;1.09&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.arterial&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;color&quot;: &quot;#e4d7c6&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;47&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.arterial&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry.stroke&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-12&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.arterial&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.icon&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.local&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;color&quot;: &quot;#fbfaf7&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;77&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.local&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry.fill&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-5&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;road.local&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry.stroke&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-15&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;transit.station.airport&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;47&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;-100&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;water&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;all&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;visibility&quot;: &quot;on&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;color&quot;: &quot;#acbcc9&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;water&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;geometry&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;53&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;water&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text.fill&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;-42&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }, {&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;saturation&quot;: &quot;17&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }, {&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;featureType&quot;: &quot;water&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;elementType&quot;: &quot;labels.text.stroke&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;      &quot;stylers&quot;: [{&#xD;&#xA;        &quot;lightness&quot;: &quot;61&quot;&#xD;&#xA;      }]&#xD;&#xA;    }],&#xD;&#xA;  };&#xD;&#xA;  map = new google.maps.Map(document.getElementById(&quot;map&quot;), myOptions);&#xD;&#xA;}&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;function codeAddress(address) {&#xD;&#xA;  geocoder.geocode({&#xD;&#xA;    'address': paddress&#xD;&#xA;  }, function(results, status) {&#xD;&#xA;    if (status == google.maps.GeocoderStatus.OK) {&#xD;&#xA;      map.setCenter(results[0].geometry.location);&#xD;&#xA;      var marker = new MarkerWithLabel({&#xD;&#xA;        position: results[0].geometry.location,&#xD;&#xA;        map: map, //Here I get the error&#xD;&#xA;        //icon: pointer, //Here I don't get any image&#xD;&#xA;        labelContent: paddress, //here I don't get any address&#xD;&#xA;        labelAnchor: new google.maps.Point(22, 0),&#xD;&#xA;        labelClass: &quot;labels&quot;,&#xD;&#xA;        labelStyle: {&#xD;&#xA;          opacity: 1.0&#xD;&#xA;        },&#xD;&#xA;      });&#xD;&#xA;    } else {&#xD;&#xA;      //alert(&quot;Geocode was not successful for the following reason: &quot; + status);&#xD;&#xA;    }&#xD;&#xA;  });&#xD;&#xA;}&#xD;&#xA;initialize_map();&#xD;&#xA;codeAddress('location');&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&quot;snippet-code-css lang-css prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;html,&#xD;&#xA;body,&#xD;&#xA;#map {&#xD;&#xA;  height: 100%;&#xD;&#xA;  width: 100%;&#xD;&#xA;  margin: 0px;&#xD;&#xA;  padding: 0px&#xD;&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&quot;snippet-code-html lang-html prettyprint-override&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;script src=&quot;https://maps.googleapis.com/maps/api/js&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;script src=&quot;https://cdn.rawgit.com/printercu/google-maps-utility-library-v3-read-only/master/markerwithlabel/src/markerwithlabel.js&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&#xD;&#xA;&amp;lt;div id=&quot;map&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1210329" LastActivityDate="2016-07-07T00:46:22.057" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="35807543" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="35807255" CreationDate="2016-03-04T22:53:32.123" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am not a smart man. I was able to figure out the answer literally 5 minutes after posting this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;objectGUID = (new VBArray(objectGUID.value)).toArray();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will convert the &lt;code&gt;[object Array of Byte]&lt;/code&gt; to a JavaScript friendly array of integers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3383907" LastActivityDate="2016-03-04T22:53:32.123" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="39013406" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2016-08-18T08:32:13.177" Score="0" ViewCount="139" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am converting my camel spring application to use spring boot latest version 1.4.0. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My application context xml is outside my WAR , to add flexibility. But I am unable to get it loaded in the project. If I add it inside my project classpath and use @ImportResource  it works fine. How do i Get it loaded from outside. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My web.xml (old one) &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    &amp;lt;?xml version=&quot;1.0&quot;?&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;!DOCTYPE web-app PUBLIC &quot;-//Sun Microsystems, Inc.//DTD Web Application 2.3//EN&quot;&#xA;                             &quot;http://java.sun.com/dtd/web-app_2_3.dtd&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;web-app&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;display-name&amp;gt;Archetype Created Web Application&amp;lt;/display-name&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;context-param&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;param-name&amp;gt;contextConfigLocation&amp;lt;/param-name&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;param-value&amp;gt;file:///${camel.config.location}&amp;lt;/param-value&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;description&amp;gt; location of spring xml files&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;/context-param&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;context-param&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;param-name&amp;gt;log4jConfigLocation&amp;lt;/param-name&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;param-value&amp;gt;file:///${log4j.config.location}&amp;lt;/param-value&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/context-param&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;context-param&amp;gt;&#xA;         &amp;lt;param-name&amp;gt;log4jRefreshInterval&amp;lt;/param-name&amp;gt;&#xA;         &amp;lt;param-value&amp;gt;10000&amp;lt;/param-value&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/context-param&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;listener&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;listener-class&amp;gt;org.springframework.web.context.ContextLoaderListener&amp;lt;/listener-class&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;/listener&amp;gt;&#xA;     &amp;lt;listener&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;listener-class&amp;gt;org.springframework.web.util.Log4jConfigListener&amp;lt;/listener-class&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;/listener&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/web-app&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have implemented the below application class after searching thru a example but the context.xml is not loaded . I have added it as a resource Loader. I used onStartup too but still noting gets loaded only spring boot loads up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    @Configuration&#xA;    @EnableAutoConfiguration(exclude = { DataSourceAutoConfiguration.class,&#xA;            DataSourceTransactionManagerAutoConfiguration.class, HibernateJpaAutoConfiguration.class })&#xA;    @ComponentScan&#xA;    public class DLBootApplication extends SpringBootServletInitializer {&#xA;&#xA;        public static void main(String[] args) throws Exception {&#xA;            final ConfigurableEnvironment environment = new StandardServletEnvironment();&#xA;            initialize(environment);&#xA;            final ResourceLoader resourceLoader = createResourceLoader();&#xA;            final ApplicationContext ctx = new SpringApplicationBuilder(DLBootApplication.class)&#xA;                    .contextClass(AnnotationConfigEmbeddedWebApplicationContext.class).environment(environment)&#xA;                    .resourceLoader(resourceLoader).run(args);&#xA;&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        public static void initialize(ConfigurableEnvironment environment) {&#xA;            final String camelConfig = environment.getProperty(Constants.DL_CAMEL_CONFIG_LOCATION);&#xA;            final String log4jConfig = environment.getProperty(Constants.DL_LOG4J_CONFIG_LOCATION);&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;            if (StringUtils.isEmpty(camelConfig)) {&#xA;                throw new IllegalStateException(Constants.DL_CAMEL_CONFIG_LOCATION + &quot; is empty&quot;);&#xA;            }&#xA;            if (StringUtils.isEmpty(log4jConfig)) {&#xA;                throw new IllegalStateException(Constants.DL_LOG4J_CONFIG_LOCATION + &quot; is empty&quot;);&#xA;            }&#xA;&#xA;            System.setProperty(Constants.DL_CAMEL_CONFIG_LOCATION, camelConfig);&#xA;            System.setProperty(Constants.DL_LOG4J_CONFIG_LOCATION, log4jConfig);&#xA;&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        public static ResourceLoader createResourceLoader() {&#xA;            final FileSystemResourceLoader resLoader = new FileSystemResourceLoader();&#xA;            resLoader.getResource(System.getProperty(Constants.DL_CAMEL_CONFIG_LOCATION));&#xA;            return resLoader;&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        @Override&#xA;        protected SpringApplicationBuilder configure(SpringApplicationBuilder application) {&#xA;            final ConfigurableEnvironment environment = new StandardServletEnvironment();&#xA;            initialize(environment);&#xA;            final ResourceLoader resourceLoader = createResourceLoader();&#xA;            return application.sources(DLBootApplication.class).environment(environment).resourceLoader(resourceLoader);&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        @Override&#xA;        public void onStartup(ServletContext servletContext) throws ServletException {&#xA;            // Create the 'root' Spring application context&#xA;            final AnnotationConfigWebApplicationContext rootContext = new AnnotationConfigWebApplicationContext();&#xA;            rootContext.register(DLBootApplication.class);&#xA;&#xA;            // Manage the lifecycle of the root application context&#xA;            servletContext.addListener(new ContextLoaderListener(rootContext));&#xA;            servletContext.addListener(new Log4jConfigListener());&#xA;&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1162108" LastActivityDate="2016-08-19T11:26:53.947" Title="spring boot - load context xml outside classpath and listeners" Tags="&lt;spring-boot&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="37866621" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37866041" CreationDate="2016-06-16T18:20:00.523" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Static checks against &lt;code&gt;Serializable&lt;/code&gt; are completely unreliable, in both directions.  The FindBugs warnings here are well-intentioned, but shouldn't stop you from using &lt;code&gt;CurrencyUnit&lt;/code&gt; as you are now.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A class can have a field&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Object aSerializableObject&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and be serializable, even though the static type of the field is not -- as long as it ensures that references placed in this field are serializable.  So the static check against &lt;code&gt;Serializable&lt;/code&gt; produces false negatives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It also produces false positives; implementing &lt;code&gt;Serializable&lt;/code&gt; is no guarantee that instances will serialize without exception; it is merely a statement of design intent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bottom line: while it masquerades as a static-typing feature, serializability is in reality a dynamic-typing feature.  Static checks (whether within the code, such as &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;T extends Serializable&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, or external checks, such as these FindBugs warnings) are merely hints as to where something might go wrong.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3553087" LastActivityDate="2016-06-16T18:20:00.523" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="15562636" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="15562606" CreationDate="2013-03-22T04:16:12.637" Score="3" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Add add = new Add();&#xA;if ( addWindow == false ) { //Thanks to @TofuBeer's comment. I didn't notice this at all.         &#xA;    add.setVisible(true);&#xA;}&#xA;else&#xA;    add.setVisible(true);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since you're using the &lt;code&gt;Add&lt;/code&gt;(which is the name of the Class itself), it is trying to invoke the method, statically, which is throwing the error as its not a static method in your class &lt;code&gt;Add&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use the instance you've created to call the method and make sure, the instance name isn't exactly the class name(class name is with capital &lt;code&gt;A&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add&lt;/strong&gt; - class name&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;add&lt;/strong&gt; - instance name (if you give &lt;code&gt;Add&lt;/code&gt; here also, it'll consider the class name instead of the instance name).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2024761" LastEditorUserId="2024761" LastEditDate="2013-03-22T04:30:27.993" LastActivityDate="2013-03-22T04:30:27.993" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="15142717" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T18:18:27.550" Score="0" ViewCount="1276" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am using the ftplib module and want to connect to FTP on my localhost. I am using the following code example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;import ftplib&#xA;f = ftplib.FTP()&#xA;f.connect(&quot;localhost&quot;)&#xA;f.login()&#xA;&#xA;ls=[]&#xA;f.retrlines('MLSD',ls.append)&#xA;for entry in ls:&#xA;    print entry&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It gives me a &lt;code&gt;socket.error: [Errno 61] Connection refused&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do i connect to my localhost and what am i doing wrong? Eventually i would want to send files from a client code to server code using ftplib, both running on the same machine. This is for a project, i know in reality you wouldn't have both on the same machine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1319424" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T18:24:33.520" Title="Connection refused FTP python 2.7" Tags="&lt;python&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="40391936" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40391785" CreationDate="2016-11-03T00:24:55.747" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Check if the single quotes are needed here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;git tag -d -- Retrofit2_Hatakontrolu&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note the use of &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/a/1192194/6309&quot;&gt;the double hyphen syntax '--'&lt;/a&gt; in order to separate the command from its parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, c&lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/a/6947297/6309&quot;&gt;heck for the presence of special characters&lt;/a&gt; in the tag name, in a Linux (Git) bash.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;export LESS=&quot;-CQaix4r&quot;&#xA;git tag|less&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the off-chance the single quotes are part of the tag name, try:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;git tag -d -- 'Retrofit2_Hatakontrolu'&#xA;# or (escaping single quotes):&#xA;git tag -d -- \'Retrofit2_Hatakontrolu\'&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6309" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T10:27:33.513" LastActivityDate="2016-11-03T00:44:09.940" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="37932527" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="34692210" CreationDate="2016-06-20T22:02:07.660" Score="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;The problem @Gaurang was solving was a problem with ADB. The reason that the build failed is because ADB times out querying for the available devices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following steps resolved this issue for me...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In Genymotion, go to Settings &gt; ADB (tab) &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Select radio option &quot;Use custom Android SDK tools&quot; and add the path to your Android SDK&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Restart Genymotion (may not totally be necessary, but I did and it worked)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If the above steps don't work, try also rebooting your machine as commenters have stated this worked for them. [Added This on Aug 10th] &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/OuxPz.png&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/OuxPz.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I found this because I realized that my adb server wasn't started. Following this SOF article (&lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/2306322/adb-wont-start&quot;&gt;Adb won&amp;#39;t start&lt;/a&gt;), I changed directory into my &lt;code&gt;{ANDROID_SDK_FOLDER}/tools&lt;/code&gt; and ran &lt;code&gt;adb kill-server&lt;/code&gt; then &lt;code&gt;adb start-server&lt;/code&gt; only to receive the error &lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;adb server version (32) doesn't match this client (36)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Searching this lead me to the following article and hence the resolution. Hope it helps someone else :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reference: &lt;a href=&quot;http://nmp90.com/2016/04/android-adb-server-version-32-doesnt-match-client-genymotion/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://nmp90.com/2016/04/android-adb-server-version-32-doesnt-match-client-genymotion/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1349269" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T12:17:28.433" LastActivityDate="2016-08-10T17:59:42.523" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="11364135" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11364032" CreationDate="2012-07-06T14:26:22.843" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Forms are just classes, and the timer on Form 2 is an object inside that class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can change the &lt;code&gt;Modifiers&lt;/code&gt; property of your timer to public, and then instantiate Form 2 inside Form 1, call the &lt;code&gt;Show()&lt;/code&gt; method of Form 2, and then access your timer object which is now public.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you have a project with 2 forms like so:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/Lp5K7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Solution Explorer&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Create a button in Form 1 like so:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/dhSzB.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Form One&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Place a timer object on Form 2 and change the access modifier like so:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/7TSNz.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Properties&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then put the following code under your button in form one:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;private void button1_Click(object sender, EventArgs e)&#xA;{&#xA;    Form2 f2 = new Form2();&#xA;    f2.Show();&#xA;    f2.timer1.Enabled = true;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now you can launch form 2 and access all of the properties on the timer on form 2 from form 1.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does this help?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="969613" LastEditorUserId="969613" LastEditDate="2012-07-06T14:31:33.953" LastActivityDate="2012-07-06T14:31:33.953" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="14461915" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14461568" CreationDate="2013-01-22T15:20:16.983" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;a bit of a vague question so here are a couple of examples&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on a class, check the parent if any child is selected, check ALL children if a parent is checked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;var checkboxHandlerObj = {&#xA;    init: function () {&#xA;        $('#customerServices input:checkbox[class=&quot;parent&quot;]').click(checkboxHandlerObj.parentClicked);&#xA;        $('#customerServices input:checkbox[class^=&quot;parent-&quot;]').click(checkboxHandlerObj.childClicked)&#xA;    },&#xA;    parentClicked: function () {&#xA;        var parentCheck = this.checked;&#xA;        $('#customerServices input:checkbox[class=&quot;parent-' + $(this).attr('id') + '&quot;]').each(function () {&#xA;            this.checked = parentCheck&#xA;        });&#xA;    },&#xA;    childClicked: function () {&#xA;        var temp = $(this).attr('class').split('-');&#xA;        var parentId = temp[1];&#xA;        $('#' + parentId)[0].checked = $('#customerServices input:checkbox[class=&quot;' + $(this).attr('class') + '&quot;]:checked').length !== 0;&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;checkboxHandlerObj.init();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;a fiddle for that:&lt;a href=&quot;http://jsfiddle.net/gfDAh/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://jsfiddle.net/gfDAh/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and here is a parent dependance model where if ANY child is unchecked, it unchecks the parent, and it has a &quot;check all children&quot; box &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$('#jobTypesMaster').click(function() {&#xA;    var iam = this.checked;&#xA;    $('.billdetail').each(function() {&#xA;        this.checked = iam;&#xA;    });&#xA;    if (!iam) {&#xA;        $('.billfinal:checkbox')[0].checked = iam;&#xA;    };&#xA;    $('.billfinal').attr('disabled', !this.checked);&#xA;    if (!iam) {&#xA;        $('.billspaid:checkbox')[0].checked = this.checked;&#xA;    };&#xA;    $('.billspaid').attr('disabled', $('.billfinal').checked);&#xA;});&#xA;$('.billdetail').click(function() {&#xA;    if ($('.billdetail:checked').length &amp;lt; $('.billdetail:checkbox').length) {&#xA;        $('.billfinal:checkbox')[0].checked = false;&#xA;        $('.billspaid:checkbox')[0].checked = false;&#xA;        $('.billfinal').attr('disabled', true);&#xA;        $('.billspaid').attr('disabled', true);&#xA;        $('#jobTypesMaster')[0].checked = false;&#xA;    }&#xA;    else {&#xA;        $('.billfinal').attr('disabled', false);&#xA;    };&#xA;});&#xA;$('.billfinal').click(function() {&#xA;    $('.billspaid:checkbox').attr('disabled', !this.checked);&#xA;    if (!this.checked) {&#xA;        $('.billspaid')[0].checked = false;&#xA;    };&#xA;});&#xA;$('.billdetail').trigger('click'); //set value based on initial checked count&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fiddle for that: &lt;a href=&quot;http://jsfiddle.net/h682v/3/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://jsfiddle.net/h682v/3/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="125981" LastActivityDate="2013-01-22T15:20:16.983" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="15767262" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="15767226" CreationDate="2013-04-02T14:51:58.637" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can set its &lt;code&gt;Build Action&lt;/code&gt; to Resource (&lt;code&gt;WPF&lt;/code&gt; only) or &lt;code&gt;Embedded Resource&lt;/code&gt;,&#xA;however, sometimes a much simpler option is to deploy images with binaries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/145752/what-are-the-various-build-action-settings-in-vs-net-project-properties-and-wh&quot;&gt;this great explanation on build actions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="407443" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T11:43:40.380" LastActivityDate="2013-04-02T15:00:23.227" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="25432140" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="25439649" CreationDate="2014-08-21T17:14:41.293" Score="0" ViewCount="40" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a view:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;var myView = Backbone.View.extend({  &#xA;el: '.class-name',&#xA;events: {&#xA;    'hover .button' : 'test'&#xA;},&#xA;test: function() {&#xA;    console.log('hi');&#xA;}&#xA;});&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible to have this view somehow automatically find all instances of '.class-name' on the page, and initialize itself for each - without me having to manually do it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How is this usually handled?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54408" LastActivityDate="2014-08-22T04:38:32.013" Title="Is it possible to auto-bind BackboneJs view to existing element(s)?" Tags="&lt;backbone.js&gt;&lt;view&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="16328123" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16328048" CreationDate="2013-05-01T23:37:25.667" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;For better reading use the following function:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;function print_array($input) {&#xA;  return '&amp;lt;pre&amp;gt;'.$print_r($input, true).'&amp;lt;/pre&amp;gt;';&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;for working with it use:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;echo print_array($array);    &#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This prints out a pre formatted array, where you dont have to look in the source to view it propperly&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1845040" LastEditorUserId="142162" LastEditDate="2013-05-01T23:39:04.620" LastActivityDate="2013-05-01T23:39:04.620" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="9484982" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9484832" CreationDate="2012-02-28T15:41:56.070" Score="1" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int main(){&#xA;&#xA;    AvlTree T ();&#xA;    Position P ();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1221397" LastActivityDate="2012-02-28T15:41:56.070" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="25381629" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25374196" CreationDate="2014-08-19T10:55:35.553" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is currently not supported. At this point it is an all or nothing deal. Please file a feature request in the issue tracker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="350428" LastActivityDate="2014-08-19T10:55:35.553" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="29987828" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="29254598" CreationDate="2015-05-01T13:34:22.540" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.mysql.com/doc/refman/5.5/en/string-functions.html#function_find-in-set&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;find_in_set&lt;/a&gt; function:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;create table merchant (sku varchar(50));&#xA;insert into merchant values ('B00TRPS43Y');&#xA;insert into merchant values ('FOOBARBAZ');&#xA;insert into merchant values ('B00TSHE1RO');&#xA;insert into merchant values ('BAZBARFOO');&#xA;&#xA;SELECT m.sku AS sku&#xA;FROM merchant m&#xA;WHERE find_in_set(&#xA;    m.sku, 'B00TSHIWCE,B00TRPS43Y,B00PGL6W6E,B00M7D93QU,B00U2E5EPA,B00TSHE1RO,B00T687TBA,B00SYFZMSS,B00SPVDTUY,B00RZY4YZG'&#xA;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Result:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sku&#xA;B00TRPS43Y&#xA;B00TSHE1RO&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4296151" LastActivityDate="2015-05-01T13:34:22.540" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="25993630" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2474824" CreationDate="2014-09-23T11:13:29.600" Score="6" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;yourTextFieldName.autocorrectionType = UITextAutocorrectionTypeNo;&#xA;yourTextFieldName.autocapitalizationType = UITextAutocapitalizationTypeNone;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3201797" LastActivityDate="2014-09-23T11:13:29.600" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="17166768" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="17166601" CreationDate="2013-06-18T10:37:41.197" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;Step 1. Use [['positions']] instead of ['positions']:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;In [30]: df2 = df.groupby(['stock','same1','same2'])[['positions']].sum()&#xA;&#xA;In [31]: df2 &#xA;Out[31]: &#xA;&#xA;                   positions&#xA;stock same1 same2               &#xA;A     AA    AAA          300 &#xA;B     BB    BBB          300 &#xA;C     CC    CCC          900 &#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 2. And then use &lt;code&gt;reset_index&lt;/code&gt; to move the index back to the column&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;In [34]: df2.reset_index()&#xA;Out[34]: &#xA;  stock same1 same2  positions&#xA;0     A    AA   AAA        300 &#xA;1     B    BB   BBB        300 &#xA;2     C    CC   CCC        900&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;EDIT&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seems my method is not so good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to @Andy and @unutbu , you can achieve your goal by more elegant ways:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;method 1:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;df.groupby(['stock', 'same1', 'same2'])['positions'].sum().reset_index()&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;method 2:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;df.groupby(['stock', 'same1', 'same2'], as_index=False)['positions'].sum()&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1426056" LastEditorUserId="1426056" LastEditDate="2013-06-18T10:50:43.040" LastActivityDate="2013-06-18T10:50:43.040" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="41772931" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="41772826" CreationDate="2017-01-20T21:52:32.863" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think you are trying to fund the sum of the total number of days? In that case you need to add each entry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;num1=input(&quot;How many days of weather do you have?&quot;)&#xA;num1=int(num1)&#xA;total=0&#xA;for num in range(1,num1+1):&#xA;    j = input(&quot;What is the rainfall for day{}?&quot;.format(num))&#xA;    total+=int(j)&#xA;&#xA;print (total)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4950204" LastEditorUserId="4950204" LastEditDate="2017-01-20T21:57:49.713" LastActivityDate="2017-01-20T21:57:49.713" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="27527524" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="27527680" CreationDate="2014-12-17T14:12:22.937" Score="-3" ViewCount="5489" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have some forms in my page made in Laravel. According to documentation, triple braces - {{{ }}} can escape the output. So when I use:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{{ Form::text('name') }}}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;can I be 100% sure that there is no possibility to insert SQL injection command into this form input?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4238915" LastActivityDate="2014-12-17T14:20:21.123" Title="Laravel - SQL injection prevention with {{{ }}}" Tags="&lt;forms&gt;&lt;laravel&gt;&lt;input&gt;&lt;sql-injection&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="4136054" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="4189634" CreationDate="2010-11-09T16:30:34.553" Score="0" ViewCount="873" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am getting the following error: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;2010-11-08 19:47:08.190 One2ThreePop[325:207] didFailToReceiveAdWithError&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:10.990 One2ThreePop[325:207] The operation couldnt be completed. Banner view is visible but does not have content&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:10.991 One2ThreePop[325:207] didFailToReceiveAdWithError&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:12.389 One2ThreePop[325:207] The operation couldnt be completed. Ad inventory unavailable&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:12.390 One2ThreePop[325:207] didFailToReceiveAdWithError&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:12.590 One2ThreePop[325:207] The operation couldnt be completed. Ad inventory unavailable&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:12.591 One2ThreePop[325:207] didFailToReceiveAdWithError&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:13.374 One2ThreePop[325:207] The operation couldnt be completed. Ad inventory unavailable&#xA;2010-11-08 19:47:13.375 One2ThreePop[325:207] didFailToReceiveAdWithError&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As noted above the didFailToReceiveAdWithError is being fired correctly. The iAds are enabled for my application through iTunes connect. I am using xCode 3.2.4 and iOS 4.1. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is my complete code for Cocos2d application: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;ABCPopAppDelegate.m&#xA;&#xA;- (void) applicationDidFinishLaunching:(UIApplication*)application&#xA;{&#xA;&#xA;CC_DIRECTOR_INIT();&#xA;&#xA;NSLog(@&quot;applicationDidFinishLaunching&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;MainViewController *controller = [[MainViewController alloc] init];&#xA;&#xA;[window addSubview: controller.view];&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;MainViewController.h&#xA;&#xA;#import &amp;lt;UIKit/UIKit.h&amp;gt;&#xA;#import &amp;lt;iAd/iAd.h&amp;gt;&#xA;#import &quot;cocos2d.h&quot;&#xA;#import &quot;ABCPopGameScene.h&quot;&#xA;&#xA;@interface MainViewController : UIViewController&amp;lt;ADBannerViewDelegate&amp;gt; {&#xA;&#xA;ADBannerView *bannerView;&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;@property (nonatomic,retain) ADBannerView *bannerView;&#xA;&#xA;@end&#xA;&#xA;MainViewController.m:&#xA;&#xA;// Implement viewDidLoad to do additional setup after loading the view, typically from a nib.&#xA;- (void)viewDidLoad {&#xA;&#xA;[super viewDidLoad];&#xA;&#xA;// Obtain the shared director in order to...&#xA;CCDirector *director = [CCDirector sharedDirector];&#xA;&#xA;// Sets landscape mode&#xA;[director setDeviceOrientation:kCCDeviceOrientationPortrait];&#xA;&#xA;// Turn on display FPS&#xA;[director setDisplayFPS:NO];&#xA;&#xA;// Turn on multiple touches&#xA;EAGLView *eaglView = [director openGLView];&#xA;[eaglView setMultipleTouchEnabled:YES];&#xA;&#xA;[self.view addSubview:eaglView];&#xA;&#xA;self.bannerView = [[ADBannerView alloc] initWithFrame:CGRectZero];&#xA;[self.bannerView setRequiredContentSizeIdentifiers:[NSSet setWithObjects:&#xA;ADBannerContentSizeIdentifier320x50,&#xA;ADBannerContentSizeIdentifier480x32, nil]];&#xA;&#xA;self.bannerView.currentContentSizeIdentifier = ADBannerContentSizeIdentifier320x50;&#xA;&#xA;[self.bannerView setDelegate:self];&#xA;&#xA;[self.view addSubview:self.bannerView];&#xA;&#xA;// [self.view addSubview:eaglView];&#xA;&#xA;// Default texture format for PNG/BMP/TIFF/JPEG/GIF images&#xA;// It can be RGBA8888, RGBA4444, RGB5_A1, RGB565&#xA;// You can change anytime.&#xA;[CCTexture2D setDefaultAlphaPixelFormat:kTexture2DPixelFormat_RGBA8888];&#xA;&#xA;[[CCDirector sharedDirector] runWithScene: [ABCPopGameScene scene]];&#xA;&#xA;NSLog(@&quot;viewDidLoad fired!&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;//[self moveBannerOffScreen];&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can see the game running but I do not see any ads displayed. Do I have to somehow position the ads or something?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3797" LastEditorUserId="54200" LastEditDate="2010-11-09T16:53:36.000" LastActivityDate="2010-11-15T22:47:41.443" Title="iAds Throwing Error" Tags="&lt;iphone&gt;&lt;cocos2d-iphone&gt;&lt;iad&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="42588350" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="42589221" CreationDate="2017-03-03T21:00:04.067" Score="0" ViewCount="91" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am having problems with my matplotlib/Pyqt. I have tried several different things like uninstalling matplotlib using conda remove and pip uninstall and then tried re-installing. When I try re-installing matplotlib through conda reinstall, I get the following error: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;IOError: [Errno 2] No such file or directory: u'C:\Anaconda2\pkgs\pandas-0.19.2-np111py27_1\info\index.json'&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I seem to be able to install matplotlib via pip install, but when I try running my code in jupyter notbook I get the following error: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;ImportError: No module named PyQt4. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any suggestions? I am using Python version 2.7.13 and Anaconda version 4.0.0 (64-bit) windows operator. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6627176" LastEditorUserId="5899161" LastEditDate="2017-03-04T03:16:50.017" LastActivityDate="2017-03-04T03:16:50.017" Title="Issues running Matplotlib/PyQt- Error" Tags="&lt;python&gt;&lt;matplotlib&gt;&lt;pyqt&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="38398654" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2016-07-15T14:28:07.870" Score="1" ViewCount="134" Body="&lt;p&gt;While trying to write a spark sql dataframe to jdbc I get the following exception:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;  at org.apache.spark.rdd.RDDOperationScope$.withScope(RDDOperationScope.scala:111)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.rdd.RDD.withScope(RDD.scala:316)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.rdd.RDD.foreachPartition(RDD.scala:918)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.DataFrame$$anonfun$foreachPartition$1.apply$mcV$sp(DataFrame.scala:1444)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.DataFrame$$anonfun$foreachPartition$1.apply(DataFrame.scala:1444)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.DataFrame$$anonfun$foreachPartition$1.apply(DataFrame.scala:1444)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.execution.SQLExecution$.withNewExecutionId(SQLExecution.scala:56)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.DataFrame.withNewExecutionId(DataFrame.scala:2086)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.DataFrame.foreachPartition(DataFrame.scala:1443)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.execution.datasources.jdbc.JdbcUtils$.saveTable(JdbcUtils.scala:276)&#xA;  at org.apache.spark.sql.DataFrameWriter.jdbc(DataFrameWriter.scala:311)&#xA;  at .....&#xA;Caused by: java.io.InvalidClassException: java.lang.Void; local class name incompatible with stream class name &quot;void&quot;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the way the dataframe is saved&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;dataFrame.write.mode(SaveMode.Append).jdbc(url, tableStatement, new Properties)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previosly this kind of exception were being solved by having the function return a certain value, but now it's out of our control.&#xA;Anyone encountered this before?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1993950" LastActivityDate="2016-07-15T14:28:07.870" Title="java.io.InvalidClassException: local class name incompatible with stream class name &quot;void&quot;" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;serialization&gt;&lt;apache-spark&gt;&lt;apache-spark-sql&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="25271804" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="25272066" CreationDate="2014-08-12T18:44:25.700" Score="0" ViewCount="148" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm currently working on a Magento installation with multiple websites and store views. I'm attempting to redesign one of the four sub websites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There has been a custom module added which appears to rewrite/extend the default top navigation menu to automatically include CMS pages and add a banner slot to the menu. The problem is that I want to restore the &lt;strong&gt;default Magento top menu&lt;/strong&gt; (i.e. no CMS pages) for a single website view.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've tried disabling the module inside System -&gt; Config -&gt; Advanced -&gt; Advanced for that website, however this seems to make the entire top navigation disappear. I believe the function I want to remove is this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php&#xA;/**&#xA; * extend functions from navigation.php&#xA; * &#xA; */&#xA;class Fvzzy_Category_Block_Navigation extends Mage_Catalog_Block_Navigation&#xA;{&#xA;    protected $_menus;&#xA;&#xA;    protected function _getCategoryMenuItemHtml($category, $level = 0, $isLast = false, $isFirst = false,&#xA;        $isOutermost = false, $outermostItemClass = '', $childrenWrapClass = '', $noEventAttributes = false)&#xA;    {&#xA;        if (!$category-&amp;gt;getIsActive()) {&#xA;            return '';&#xA;        }&#xA;        $html = array();&#xA;&#xA;        // get all children&#xA;        if (Mage::helper('catalog/category_flat')-&amp;gt;isEnabled()) {&#xA;            $children = (array)$category-&amp;gt;getChildrenNodes();&#xA;            $childrenCount = count($children);&#xA;        } else {&#xA;            $children = $category-&amp;gt;getChildren();&#xA;            $childrenCount = $children-&amp;gt;count();&#xA;        }&#xA;        $hasChildren = ($children &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $childrenCount);&#xA;&#xA;        // select active children&#xA;        $activeChildren = array();&#xA;        foreach ($children as $child) {&#xA;            if ($child-&amp;gt;getIsActive()) {&#xA;                $activeChildren[] = $child;&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;        $activeChildrenCount = count($activeChildren);&#xA;        $hasActiveChildren = ($activeChildrenCount &amp;gt; 0);&#xA;&#xA;        // prepare list item html classes&#xA;        $classes = array();&#xA;        $classes[] = 'level' . $level;&#xA;        //$classes[] = 'nav-' . $this-&amp;gt;_getItemPosition($level);&#xA;        $text = preg_replace('/[^A-Za-z0-9]/i', '-', strtolower($category-&amp;gt;getName()));&#xA;        //$classes[] = $category-&amp;gt;;&#xA;        if ($this-&amp;gt;isCategoryActive($category)) {&#xA;            $classes[] = 'active';&#xA;        }&#xA;        $linkClass = '';&#xA;        if ($isOutermost &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $outermostItemClass) {&#xA;            $classes[] = $outermostItemClass;&#xA;            $linkClass = ' class=&quot;'.$outermostItemClass.'&quot;';&#xA;        }&#xA;        if ($isFirst) {&#xA;            $classes[] = 'first';&#xA;        }&#xA;        if ($isLast) {&#xA;            //$classes[] = 'last';&#xA;        }&#xA;        if ($hasActiveChildren) {&#xA;            $classes[] = 'parent';&#xA;        }&#xA;        if(strtolower($text) == 'sale') $classes[] = strtolower($text);&#xA;        // prepare list item attributes&#xA;        $attributes = array();&#xA;        if (count($classes) &amp;gt; 0) {&#xA;            $attributes['class'] = implode(' ', $classes);&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        if ($hasActiveChildren &amp;amp;&amp;amp; !$noEventAttributes) {&#xA;             $attributes['onmouseover'] = 'toggleMenu(this,1)';&#xA;             $attributes['onmouseout'] = 'toggleMenu(this,0)';&#xA;        }&#xA;        // assemble list item with attributes&#xA;        $htmlLi = '&amp;lt;li';&#xA;        foreach ($attributes as $attrName =&amp;gt; $attrValue) {&#xA;            $htmlLi .= ' ' . $attrName . '=&quot;' . str_replace('&quot;', '\&quot;', $attrValue) . '&quot;';&#xA;        }&#xA;        $htmlLi .= '&amp;gt;';&#xA;        $html[] = $htmlLi;&#xA;&#xA;        $html[] = '&amp;lt;a href=&quot;'.$this-&amp;gt;getCategoryUrl($category).'&quot;'.$linkClass.'&amp;gt;';&#xA;        $html[] = '&amp;lt;span&amp;gt;' . $this-&amp;gt;escapeHtml($category-&amp;gt;getName()) . '&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;';&#xA;        $html[] = '&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;';&#xA;&#xA;        // render children&#xA;        $htmlChildren = '';&#xA;        $j = 0;&#xA;        foreach ($activeChildren as $child) {&#xA;            $htmlChildren .= $this-&amp;gt;_getCategoryMenuItemHtml(&#xA;                $child,&#xA;                ($level + 1),&#xA;                ($j == $activeChildrenCount - 1),&#xA;                ($j == 0),&#xA;                false,&#xA;                $outermostItemClass,&#xA;                $childrenWrapClass,&#xA;                $noEventAttributes&#xA;            );&#xA;            $j++;&#xA;        }&#xA;        $promotion = $this-&amp;gt;addPromotions($category-&amp;gt;getId());&#xA;        if (!empty($htmlChildren)) {&#xA;            if ($childrenWrapClass) {&#xA;                $html[] = '&amp;lt;div class=&quot;' . $childrenWrapClass . '&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;            }&#xA;            $html[] = '&amp;lt;ul class=&quot;level' . $level . '&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;menu-text&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;            if($promotion) $html[] = '';&#xA;            $html[] = $htmlChildren;&#xA;            if($promotion) $html[] = '';&#xA;            if($promotion) $html[] = '&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li class=&quot;level1 parent menu-promotion&quot;&amp;gt;'.$promotion.'&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;';&#xA;            $html[] = '&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;';&#xA;            if ($childrenWrapClass) {&#xA;                $html[] = '&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;';&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        $html[] = '&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;';&#xA;&#xA;        $html = implode(&quot;\n&quot;, $html);&#xA;        return $html;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public function renderCategoriesMenuHtml($level = 0, $outermostItemClass = '', $childrenWrapClass = '')&#xA;    {&#xA;        $activeCategories = array();&#xA;        foreach ($this-&amp;gt;getStoreCategories() as $child) {&#xA;            if ($child-&amp;gt;getIsActive()) {&#xA;                $activeCategories[] = $child;&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;        $activeCategoriesCount = count($activeCategories);&#xA;        $hasActiveCategoriesCount = ($activeCategoriesCount &amp;gt; 0);&#xA;&#xA;        if (!$hasActiveCategoriesCount) {&#xA;            return '';&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        $html = '';&#xA;        $j = 0;&#xA;        foreach ($activeCategories as $category) {&#xA;            $html .= $this-&amp;gt;_getCategoryMenuItemHtml(&#xA;                $category,&#xA;                $level,&#xA;                ($j == $activeCategoriesCount - 1),&#xA;                ($j == 0),&#xA;                true,&#xA;                $outermostItemClass,&#xA;                $childrenWrapClass,&#xA;                true&#xA;            );&#xA;            $j++;&#xA;        }&#xA;        //main store&#xA;        if(Mage::app()-&amp;gt;getStore()) $html .= $this-&amp;gt;addMenu($childrenWrapClass,Mage::app()-&amp;gt;getStore());&#xA;        return $html;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    protected function addPromotions($id = 0){&#xA;        if($id){&#xA;            $base = Mage::getBaseUrl('media',true).'promotion_box_images/';&#xA;            $file_base = Mage::getBaseDir('media').'/promotion_box_images';&#xA;            $html = ''; $img = '';&#xA;            $promotion = Mage::getModel('promotion/box')-&amp;gt;getCollection()-&amp;gt;addFieldToFilter('menu_ids',array(&#xA;                array('like'=&amp;gt;$id),&#xA;                array('like'=&amp;gt;$id.',%'),&#xA;                array('like'=&amp;gt;'%,'.$id.',%'),&#xA;                array('like'=&amp;gt;'%,'.$id)))-&amp;gt;setOrder('position')-&amp;gt;getFirstItem(); //default is desc&#xA;            if($promotion &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $promotion-&amp;gt;getId()){&#xA;                $type=$promotion-&amp;gt;getDisplayType();&#xA;                $link = ''; $img = ''; $content = ''; $width = '';&#xA;                if(file_exists($file_base.'/'.$promotion-&amp;gt;getImage())){&#xA;                    list($width) = getimagesize($file_base.'/'.$promotion-&amp;gt;getImage());&#xA;                }&#xA;                if($type!=null){&#xA;                    switch($type){&#xA;                        case 0:&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getImage()!='') $img = '&amp;lt;img src=&quot;'.$base.$promotion-&amp;gt;getImage().'&quot; alt=&quot;'.$promotion-&amp;gt;getTitle().'&quot; width=&quot;'.$width.'&quot;/&amp;gt;';&#xA;                            if(trim($promotion-&amp;gt;getLink())!='') $link = $promotion-&amp;gt;getLink();&#xA;                            break;&#xA;                        case 1:&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getImage()!='') $img = '&amp;lt;img src=&quot;'.$base.$promotion-&amp;gt;getImage().'&quot; alt=&quot;'.$promotion-&amp;gt;getTitle().'&quot; width=&quot;'.$width.'&quot;/&amp;gt;';&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getCategoryId()){&#xA;                                $c = Mage::getModel('catalog/category')-&amp;gt;load($promotion-&amp;gt;getCategoryId());&#xA;                                if($c-&amp;gt;getId() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $c-&amp;gt;getIsActive()) $link = Mage::helper('catalog/category')-&amp;gt;getCategoryUrl($c);&#xA;                            }&#xA;                            break;&#xA;                        case 2:&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getImage()!='') $img = '&amp;lt;img src=&quot;'.$base.$promotion-&amp;gt;getImage().'&quot; alt=&quot;'.$promotion-&amp;gt;getTitle().'&quot; width=&quot;'.$width.'&quot;/&amp;gt;';&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getProductSku()){&#xA;                                $id = Mage::getModel('catalog/product')-&amp;gt;getIdBySku($promotion-&amp;gt;getProductSku());&#xA;                                $p = Mage::getModel('catalog/product')-&amp;gt;load($id);&#xA;                                if($p-&amp;gt;getId()) $link = $p-&amp;gt;getProductUrl();&#xA;                            }&#xA;                            break;&#xA;                        case 3:&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getImage()!='') $img = '&amp;lt;img src=&quot;'.$base.$promotion-&amp;gt;getImage().'&quot; alt=&quot;'.$promotion-&amp;gt;getTitle().'&quot; width=&quot;'.$width.'&quot;/&amp;gt;';&#xA;                            if($promotion-&amp;gt;getPageId()){&#xA;                                $_link = Mage::Helper('cms/page')-&amp;gt;getPageUrl($promotion-&amp;gt;getPageId());&#xA;                                                                if($_link != ''){ &#xA;                                                                $nodes = Mage::getModel('enterprise_cms/hierarchy_node')-&amp;gt;getCollection()&#xA;                                                                  -&amp;gt;addFieldToFilter('page_id', array('eq' =&amp;gt; $promotion-&amp;gt;getPageId()));&#xA;                                                            foreach($nodes as $_node){&#xA;                                                                $link = $_node-&amp;gt;getRequestUrl();&#xA;                                                            }&#xA;                                                            if(!$link){$link = Mage::Helper('cms/page')-&amp;gt;getPageUrl($promotion-&amp;gt;getPageId());}&#xA;                                                                }&#xA;                            }&#xA;                            break;&#xA;                        case 4:&#xA;                            $content = $promotion-&amp;gt;getContent();&#xA;                            break;&#xA;                    }&#xA;                }&#xA;                if($img &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $link){&#xA;                    $html = '&amp;lt;a href=&quot;'.$link.'&quot;&amp;gt;'.$img.'&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;';&#xA;                }&#xA;                elseif($img){&#xA;                    $html = '&amp;lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&amp;gt;'.$img.'&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;';&#xA;                }&#xA;                else{&#xA;                    $html = $content;&#xA;                }&#xA;            }&#xA;            return $html;&#xA;        }else{return false;}&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    //$menu = array( array('label'=&amp;gt;'News','href'=&amp;gt;'blog','module'=&amp;gt;'blog','sub'=&amp;gt;array(array('label'=&amp;gt;'submenu','href'=&amp;gt;'blog2','module'=&amp;gt;'blog'))) );&#xA;    public function setOtherMenu($menu){&#xA;        $this-&amp;gt;_menus = $menu;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public function addMenu( $childrenWrapClass = '', $store ) {&#xA;&#xA;            $this-&amp;gt;_node_ids = array();&#xA;            $current_module = $this-&amp;gt;getRequest()-&amp;gt;getModuleName();&#xA;            $page_id = $this-&amp;gt;getRequest()-&amp;gt;getParam('page_id');&#xA;&#xA;            // get all the cms page nodes not folder or containers&#xA;            $nodes = Mage::getModel('enterprise_cms/hierarchy_node')-&amp;gt;getCollection()&#xA;                                                                    -&amp;gt;joinMetaData()&#xA;                                                                    -&amp;gt;addFieldToFilter( 'level', 1 )&#xA;                                                                    //-&amp;gt;addFieldToFilter( 'menu_visibility', 1 )&#xA;                                                                    -&amp;gt;addFieldToFilter( 'main_table.page_id', array( 'notnull' =&amp;gt; true ))&#xA;                                                                    -&amp;gt;setOrder('sort_order','ASC');&#xA;&#xA;            if ( $store instanceof Mage_Core_Model_Store ) {&#xA;                $store = $store-&amp;gt;getId();&#xA;                $storeIds = array( 0, $store );&#xA;                $nodes-&amp;gt;getSelect()&#xA;                      -&amp;gt;joinLeft( array( 'cs' =&amp;gt; 'cms_page_store' ), 'main_table.page_id=cs.page_id', array( 'cs.store_id' ) )&#xA;                      -&amp;gt;where( 'cs.store_id IN ('. implode( ',', $storeIds ) .')' ); // not the best sql here but it works as store id will be one at a time.&#xA;            }&#xA;&#xA;            $active_node = Mage::registry('current_cms_hierarchy_node');&#xA;            $active_node_ids = array();&#xA;            if($active_node){&#xA;                $xpath = $active_node-&amp;gt;getXpath();&#xA;                $all = explode( '/', $xpath );&#xA;                foreach ( $all as $index ) $active_node_ids[] = $index;&#xA;            }&#xA;            $this-&amp;gt;_node_ids = $active_node_ids;&#xA;            if ( $this-&amp;gt;_menus ) {&#xA;                $menus = $this-&amp;gt;_menus;&#xA;            }&#xA;            else {&#xA;                $menus = array();&#xA;            }&#xA;&#xA;            $links = '';&#xA;            foreach ( $nodes as $node ) {&#xA;                $tree = $node-&amp;gt;setCollectActivePagesOnly(true)&#xA;                             -&amp;gt;setCollectIncludedPagesOnly(true)&#xA;                             -&amp;gt;setTreeMaxDepth(0)&#xA;                             -&amp;gt;setTreeIsBrief(1) //this way it won't show the container link&#xA;                             -&amp;gt;getTreeSlice(0, 1); //up to tree top and down to one level&#xA;                $links .= $this-&amp;gt;drawCmsMenu($tree,0,1,$childrenWrapClass);&#xA;            }&#xA;            foreach ( $menus as $menu ) {&#xA;                if(isset($menu['sub'])) $has_sub_class = ' parent'; else $has_sub_class = '';&#xA;                if (isset($menu['module']) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $current_module == $menu['module'] ) {&#xA;                    $links .= '&amp;lt;li class=&quot;level0 level-top active'.$has_sub_class.'&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;                }&#xA;                else {&#xA;                    $links .= '&amp;lt;li class=&quot;level0 level-top'.$has_sub_class.'&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;                }&#xA;                $html = '';&#xA;                if(isset($menu['sub']) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; is_array($menu['sub'])){&#xA;                    $submenu = $menu['sub'];&#xA;                    $html .= '&amp;lt;div class=&quot;'.$childrenWrapClass.'&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ul class=&quot;level0&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;                    foreach($submenu as $sub){&#xA;                         if(is_array($sub) &amp;amp;&amp;amp;isset($sub['href']) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isset($sub['label']))&#xA;                                                        //2012-11-20 AU TEAM coding for change &amp;lt;h2&amp;gt; -&amp;gt; &amp;lt;span&amp;gt;&#xA;                            $html .= '&amp;lt;li class=&quot;level1&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;'.Mage::getBaseUrl().$sub['href'].'&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span&amp;gt;'.$sub['label'].'&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;';&#xA;                    }&#xA;                    $html .= '&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;';&#xA;                }&#xA;                if(isset($menu['href']) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isset($menu['label']))&#xA;                    $links .= '&amp;lt;a class=&quot;level-top&quot; href=&quot;'.Mage::getBaseUrl().$menu['href'].'&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span&amp;gt;'.$menu['label'].'&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;';&#xA;                //add submenu&#xA;                if($html != '') $links .= $html;&#xA;                $links .= '&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;';&#xA;            }&#xA;            return $links;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    /* Add Maximal Depth filter&#xA;     * 2012.04.11 by Bruce&#xA;     */&#xA;    public function drawCmsMenu( array $tree, $parentNodeId = 0, $level = 0, $childrenWrapClass = '' ) {&#xA;&#xA;        $html = '';&#xA;&#xA;        if ( !isset($tree[$parentNodeId ])) return $html;&#xA;&#xA;        foreach ( $tree[ $parentNodeId ] as $nodeId =&amp;gt; $node ) {&#xA;            /* @var $node Enterprise_Cms_Model_Hierarchy_Node */&#xA;            $nested = $this-&amp;gt;drawCmsMenu( $tree, $nodeId, $node-&amp;gt;getLevel()+1, $childrenWrapClass);&#xA;            $hasChildren = ( $nested != '' );&#xA;            // set style classes&#xA;            $class = array();&#xA;            $class[] = 'level'. ( $level - 1 );&#xA;            if ( $level - 1 == 0 )&#xA;                $class[] = 'level-top';&#xA;            if ( $this-&amp;gt;_node_ids &amp;amp;&amp;amp; in_array( $node-&amp;gt;getNodeId(), $this-&amp;gt;_node_ids ) )&#xA;                $class[] = 'active';&#xA;            if ( $hasChildren )&#xA;                $class[] = 'parent';&#xA;            // li wrapper header&#xA;            $html .= '&amp;lt;li class=&quot;'. implode( ' ', $class ) .'&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;            $html .= $this-&amp;gt;_getNodeLabel( $node, $level - 1 );&#xA;            // div wrapper header&#xA;            if ( $hasChildren ){&#xA;                if ( $childrenWrapClass ) $html .= '&amp;lt;div class=&quot;'. $childrenWrapClass .'&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;                $html .= '&amp;lt;ul class=&quot;level'. ( $level - 1 ) .'&quot;&amp;gt;';&#xA;            }&#xA;            // children&#xA;            $html .= $nested;&#xA;            // div wrapper footer&#xA;            if ( $hasChildren ) {&#xA;                $html.='&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;';&#xA;                if ( $childrenWrapClass ) $html .= '&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;';&#xA;            }&#xA;            // li wrapper footer&#xA;            $html .= '&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;';&#xA;        }&#xA;        return $html;&#xA;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    protected function _getNodeLabel($node,$level)&#xA;    {&#xA;        if($level==0) $class = 'level-top'; else $class = '';&#xA;        if($node-&amp;gt;getPageTitle()) return '&amp;lt;a class=&quot;'.$class.'&quot; href=&quot;'.$node-&amp;gt;getUrl().'&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span&amp;gt;'.$node-&amp;gt;getPageTitle().'&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;';&#xA;        else return '&amp;lt;a class=&quot;'.$class.'&quot; href=&quot;'.$node-&amp;gt;getUrl().'&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span&amp;gt;'.$node-&amp;gt;getLabel().'&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;';&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know that the config file for this module looks like the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?xml version=&quot;1.0&quot;?&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;config&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;modules&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;Fvzzy_Category&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;0.1.0&amp;lt;/version&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/Fvzzy_Category&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/modules&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;global&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;blocks&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;fvzzy_category&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;class&amp;gt;Fvzzy_Category_Block&amp;lt;/class&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;/fvzzy_category&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;catalog&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;rewrite&amp;gt;&#xA;                    &amp;lt;navigation&amp;gt;Fvzzy_Category_Block_Navigation&amp;lt;/navigation&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;/rewrite&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;/catalog&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/blocks&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;resources&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;fvzzy_category_setup&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;setup&amp;gt;&#xA;                    &amp;lt;module&amp;gt;Fvzzy_Category&amp;lt;/module&amp;gt;&#xA;                    &amp;lt;class&amp;gt;Mage_Catalog_Model_Resource_Eav_Mysql4_Setup&amp;lt;/class&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;/setup&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;/fvzzy_category_setup&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/resources&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/global&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/config&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And that if I'm able to remove the following part from that file, I get my intended outcome:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;            &amp;lt;catalog&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;rewrite&amp;gt;&#xA;                    &amp;lt;navigation&amp;gt;Fvzzy_Category_Block_Navigation&amp;lt;/navigation&amp;gt;&#xA;                &amp;lt;/rewrite&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;/catalog&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The problem is, I just want to get the top navigation menu function restored back to normal for &lt;strong&gt;one&lt;/strong&gt; website view.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is there any way to overwrite that navigation rewrite event for one store/website view?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If not, is it possible to disable this module without it disabling my whole top menu for that website view?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've tried completely duplicating the module, disabling the original one and enabling the new one in my desired website but that also appears to be making the top menu disappear entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm really not sure what else to do with this - if anyone is able to help it would be hugely appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2098191" LastActivityDate="2014-08-12T19:01:35.490" Title="Restore standard Mage_Catalog_Block_Navigation functionality in top navigation for a single website in a multi-store Magento installation" Tags="&lt;php&gt;&lt;magento&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="573518" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="573526" CreationDate="2009-02-21T18:34:25.517" Score="1" ViewCount="9047" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to know the best way about when we want to bind a dataTable generated based on a searchResult to a gridview ( &lt;em&gt;Just for now we want to show one record&lt;/em&gt; ) ,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;now how can we add &lt;strong&gt;edit-delete capability&lt;/strong&gt; for this record shown in the gridview ?&#xA;How many ways do we have for this , &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know some but I want to reshape my knowledge , and find better ways &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;( the information will be bound after user clicked a button . )&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50506" OwnerDisplayName="Sypress" LastActivityDate="2014-07-15T04:41:56.990" Title="Bind a DataTable to a gridview and add Edit Capability to the grid" Tags="&lt;asp.net&gt;&lt;gridview&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="32689664" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28951786" CreationDate="2015-09-21T07:32:54.067" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is what PostgreSQL official docs says:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Databases are physically separated and access control is managed at the connection level. If one PostgreSQL server instance is to house projects or users that should be separate and for the most part unaware of each other, it is therefore recommendable to put them into separate databases. If the projects or users are interrelated and should be able to use each other's resources they should be put in the same database, but possibly into separate schemas. Schemas are a purely logical structure and who can access what is managed by the privilege system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.postgresql.org/docs/8.0/static/managing-databases.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.postgresql.org/docs/8.0/static/managing-databases.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2086860" LastActivityDate="2015-09-21T07:32:54.067" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="19421173" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-10-17T07:58:11.303" Score="1" ViewCount="1853" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have been trying many different solutions found here but none works. I want to convert the string to the format of dd/MM/yyyy&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;editField[&quot;ExpiryTime&quot;] = &quot;5/19/2011 12:00:00 AM&quot;;&#xA;DateTime dt = DateTime.ParseExact(editField[&quot;ExpiryTime&quot;].ToString(), &quot;dd/MM/yyyy HH:mm:ss tt&quot;,  CultureInfo.InvariantCulture);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I always get an error of invalid System.DateTime. Pleaes help!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1109363" LastActivityDate="2013-10-17T08:08:58.337" Title="convert string to datetime format invalid System.Datetime" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="14343801" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-01-15T17:55:25.350" Score="0" ViewCount="749" Body="&lt;p&gt;When I expand the combobox list I should see items such as &quot;one&quot; &quot;two&quot; &quot;three&quot;, but when I select, say,  &quot;one&quot; and collapse the combobox, I would like to see &quot;1&quot; on display instead of &quot;one&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have tried adding a &lt;code&gt;ListDataListener&lt;/code&gt; to the combobox and inside &lt;code&gt;contentsChanged()&lt;/code&gt; I do &#xA;&lt;code&gt;box.getEditor().setItem(my_map.get(&quot;one&quot;))&lt;/code&gt; where my_map stores the mappings from &quot;one&quot; to &quot;1&quot; etc. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, it does not work and I don't know why.. Does something happen after &lt;code&gt;contentsChanged()&lt;/code&gt; is called that overwrites my changes? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any ideas? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1861088" LastEditorUserId="714968" LastEditDate="2013-01-15T18:13:36.763" LastActivityDate="2013-01-15T18:32:49.333" Title="Let JComboBox change displayed item upon item selection" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;swing&gt;&lt;jcombobox&gt;&lt;listeners&gt;&lt;changelistener&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="37529977" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="37530130" CreationDate="2016-05-30T16:14:30.977" Score="0" ViewCount="293" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can't set publicPort and privatePort for container in docker.&#xA;I creating docker container with java library &lt;code&gt;docker-client&lt;/code&gt; for java &#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/spotify/docker-client&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://github.com/spotify/docker-client&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I already had created a docker image locally &quot;mobillogix/selenium-chrome&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DockerClient docker = DefaultDockerClient.fromEnv().build();&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    // Bind container ports to host ports&#xA;    final String[] ports = {&quot;44444&quot;, &quot;59004&quot;};&#xA;    final String[] ports1 = {&quot;4444&quot;, &quot;5900&quot;};&#xA;&#xA;    final Map&amp;lt;String, List&amp;lt;PortBinding&amp;gt;&amp;gt; portBindings = new HashMap&amp;lt;String, List&amp;lt;PortBinding&amp;gt;&amp;gt;();&#xA;    for (String port : ports) {&#xA;        List&amp;lt;PortBinding&amp;gt; hostPorts = new ArrayList&amp;lt;PortBinding&amp;gt;();&#xA;        hostPorts.add(PortBinding.of(&quot;0.0.0.0&quot;, port));&#xA;        portBindings.put(port, hostPorts);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    final HostConfig hostConfig = HostConfig.builder().portBindings(portBindings).build();&#xA;&#xA;    final ContainerConfig containerConfig = ContainerConfig.builder()&#xA;            .hostConfig(hostConfig)&#xA;            .image(&quot;mobillogix/selenium-chrome&quot;).exposedPorts(ports1)&#xA;            .build();&#xA;&#xA;    final ContainerCreation creation = docker.createContainer(containerConfig);&#xA;    final String id = creation.id();&#xA;&#xA;    // Start container&#xA;    docker.startContainer(id);&#xA;&#xA;    final List&amp;lt;Container&amp;gt; containers = docker.listContainers();&#xA;&#xA;    webDriver();&#xA;&#xA;    // Kill container&#xA;    docker.killContainer(id);&#xA;&#xA;    // Remove container&#xA;    docker.removeContainer(id);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This code create container:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;CONTAINER ID        IMAGE                        COMMAND                  CREATED             STATUS              PORTS                NAMES&#xA;6beec961dfcf        mobillogix/selenium-chrome   &quot;/opt/bin/entry_point&quot;   4 seconds ago       Up 2 seconds        4444/tcp, 5900/tcp   elegant_kare&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;with ports &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;4444/tcp, 5900/tcp&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but I want to create container with ports:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;0.0.0.0:44444-&gt;4444/tcp, 0.0.0.0:59004-&gt;5900/tc&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2772562" LastEditorUserId="2772562" LastEditDate="2016-05-31T08:39:53.197" LastActivityDate="2016-05-31T08:39:53.197" Title="Set ports for container in docker for docker-client for java" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;docker&gt;&lt;docker-compose&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="29084432" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="29084015" CreationDate="2015-03-16T18:35:37.967" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Actually found the answer  you have to return this explicitly at the end of controller.Haven't found the details, but it looks that depending on the return result the framework decides whether to add it to scope or not. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1432672" LastActivityDate="2015-03-16T18:35:37.967" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="6872517" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6871960" CreationDate="2011-07-29T11:36:34.873" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'll post you a small example, feel free to adjust to your needs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int width = 1024;&#xA;int height = 768;&#xA;FrameLayout fl = (FrameLayout) findViewById(R.id.mainframe);&#xA;&#xA;fl.setLayoutParams(new FrameLayout.LayoutParams(width, height));&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want you can use match_parrent instead of width and height ofc, or anything else that xml can do&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="850447" LastEditorUserId="507519" LastEditDate="2012-01-07T01:54:21.690" LastActivityDate="2012-01-07T01:54:21.690" CommentCount="16" />
  <row Id="26851096" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="26852152" CreationDate="2014-11-10T19:08:26.750" Score="1" ViewCount="568" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am writing app for myself and wondering what is the best approach to validate username/password length while I use JPA with Hibernate? &#xA;Firsty I thought to add @Column(length = 20) (you have to know that my app consists of RESTful services) but when someone tries to add User entity, whose username is longer than 20 characters it causes DataIntegrityViolationException. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know I could handle this in Spring UserController, but it is not clear in my opinion. This exception can mean actually problem with everything (everything that refers to User entity).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can also validate username before persisting it to database (maybe create and throw some UsernameSizeExceededException or something like that) but I am quite sure, that JPA developers has already found the way to this situation &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What can you recommend me? &#xA;Thanks! :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3161589" LastActivityDate="2014-11-10T20:31:15.763" Title="Best way to validate username length in JPA, Hibernate" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;spring&gt;&lt;hibernate&gt;&lt;jpa&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="42076202" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-02-06T19:57:29.470" Score="0" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm finishing a project, but I have one more step to finish.&#xA;I want to visualize microphone input by a canvas.&#xA;Getting the data from the microphone isn't a problem.&#xA;But I want to visualize it in a special way. (see image)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/YPcwN.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wave&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to animate each element from the wave.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My problem isn't the animation.&#xA;My problem is to create those shapes in the CANVAS. &#xA;This is an example of one shape:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/oq2B6.png&quot; alt=&quot;One shape&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can create a rounded corner shape with the canvas&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    const draw = () =&amp;gt; {&#xA;        fillRoundedRect(20, 20, 100, 100, 20);&#xA;        ctx.fillStyle = &quot;red&quot;;&#xA;        ctx.fill();&#xA;    };&#xA;&#xA;    const fillRoundedRect = (x, y, w, h, r) =&amp;gt; {&#xA;        ctx.beginPath();&#xA;        ctx.moveTo(x+r, y);&#xA;        ctx.lineTo(x+w-r, y);&#xA;        ctx.quadraticCurveTo(x+w, y, x+w, y+r);&#xA;        ctx.lineTo(x+w, y+h-r);&#xA;        ctx.quadraticCurveTo(x+w, y+h, x+w-r, y+h);&#xA;        ctx.lineTo(x+r, y+h);&#xA;        ctx.quadraticCurveTo(x, y+h, x, y+h-r);&#xA;        ctx.lineTo(x, y+r);&#xA;        ctx.quadraticCurveTo(x, y, x+r, y);&#xA;        ctx.fill();&#xA;    };&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can someone help me with creating a shape like in the second image?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance guys!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6252523" LastEditorUserId="4571082" LastEditDate="2017-02-06T20:29:32.340" LastActivityDate="2017-02-28T23:42:49.497" Title="Canvas special shape - animating" Tags="&lt;javascript&gt;&lt;html5&gt;&lt;canvas&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="17596894" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="17596511" CreationDate="2013-07-11T15:01:37.583" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$string = '&#xA;    code=jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;    code=jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;    code=jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;    code=jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;    ';&#xA;&#xA;preg_match_all('/(?&amp;lt;=code=)[a-zA-Z0-9]+/', $string, $matches);&#xA;&#xA;echo('&amp;lt;pre&amp;gt;');&#xA;print_r($matches);&#xA;echo('&amp;lt;/pre&amp;gt;');&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Outputs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Array&#xA;(&#xA;    [0] =&amp;gt; Array&#xA;        (&#xA;            [0] =&amp;gt; jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;            [1] =&amp;gt; jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;            [2] =&amp;gt; jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;            [3] =&amp;gt; jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&#xA;        )&#xA;)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However without a suffixing delimiter, it won't work correctly if this pattern is concatenated, eg: &lt;code&gt;code=jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435code=jhb2345jhbv2345ljhb2435&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But perhaps that won't be a problem for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1692906" LastActivityDate="2013-07-11T15:01:37.583" CommentCount="1" />
</posts>
